<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><atom:link href="https://rsseverything.com/feed/5a44e712-2dce-412c-8683-f6fa58f0280c.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>高影响力研究-生物统计学</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/pages/highly_cited_articles <description><![CDATA[Explore a collection of the most read and most cited articles making an impact in Biostatistics published within the past two years.]]></description><lastbuilddate> 2024 年 7 月 15 日星期一 22:37:02 -0400</lastbuilddate><generator> RSS 一切</generator><ttl>360</ttl><item><guid ispermalink="false"> c81a9bf044eec983dbdc2ea6408e6962</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jun 2024 10:16:18 -0400</pubDate><title> googletag.cmd.push(function () { googletag.display(&#39;adBlockHeader&#39;); });</title><link/> #skipNav&quot; class=&quot;skipnav <description><![CDATA[Cluster randomized trials often exhibit a three-level structure with participants nested in subclusters such as health care providers, and subclusters nested in clusters such as clinics. While the average treatment effect has been the primary focus in planning three-level randomized trials, interest is growing in ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 6e9a2167f30d766b6bc651cbd4e1e271</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jun 2024 10:15:56 -0400</pubDate><title>将暴露不确定性纳入健康分析并应用于空气污染和死产的贝叶斯框架</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/25/1/20/6671878?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Studies of the relationships between environmental exposures and adverse health outcomes often rely on a two-stage statistical modeling approach, where exposure is modeled/predicted in the first stage and used as input to a separately fit health outcome analysis in the second stage. Uncertainty in these predictions is ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 0a34f0c7380011becd4b8519fe498304</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jun 2024 10:15:50 -0400</pubDate><title> CGR-CUSUM：连续时间广义快速响应累积和图</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/25/1/253/6705266?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Rapidly detecting problems in the quality of care is of utmost importance for the well-being of patients. Without proper inspection schemes, such problems can go undetected for years. Cumulative sum (CUSUM) charts have proven to be useful for quality control, yet available methodology for survival outcomes is limited. The ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 1c2b05e985722eec073161565c2d51cd</guid><pubDate> Sat, 29 Jun 2024 10:16:47 -0400</pubDate><title>单细胞 RNA 测序数据的潜在变量估计后的推断</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/25/1/270/6893953?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[In the analysis of single-cell RNA sequencing data, researchers often characterize the variation between cells by estimating a latent variable, such as cell type or pseudotime, representing some aspect of the cell’s state. They then test each gene for association with the estimated latent variable. If the same data are ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 6913c4e80ddb13a70ce9f809dab09386</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jun 2024 10:15:45 -0400</pubDate><title> DeLIVR：一种 IV 回归的深度学习方法，用于测试全转录组关联研究中的非线性因果效应</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/25/2/468/6968926?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Transcriptome-wide association studies (TWAS) have been increasingly applied to identify (putative) causal genes for complex traits and diseases. TWAS can be regarded as a two-sample two-stage least squares method for instrumental variable (IV) regression for causal inference. The standard TWAS (called TWAS-L) only ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 0a9828cff871856b3f2f5f817b10077f</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jun 2024 10:15:38 -0400</pubDate><title>平台研究中代孕的灵活评估</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/25/1/220/6968929?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Trial-level surrogates are useful tools for improving the speed and cost effectiveness of trials but surrogates that have not been properly evaluated can cause misleading results. The evaluation procedure is often contextual and depends on the type of trial setting. There have been many proposed methods for trial-level ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> fe9acaaf029b24d57dce05f60b47d36c</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jun 2024 10:15:35 -0400</pubDate><title>使用贝叶斯方法估算 COVID-19 发病率和感染死亡率</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/25/2/354/7070649?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Naive estimates of incidence and infection fatality rates (IFR) of coronavirus disease 2019 suffer from a variety of biases, many of which relate to preferential testing. This has motivated epidemiologists from around the globe to conduct serosurveys that measure the immunity of individuals by testing for the presence of ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> c26ab5d54d6d20af9175f5069464b31c</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jun 2024 10:15:30 -0400</pubDate><title>因果解释荟萃分析中系统性缺失数据</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/25/2/289/7091872?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Causally interpretable meta-analysis combines information from a collection of randomized controlled trials to estimate treatment effects in a target population in which experimentation may not be possible but from which covariate information can be obtained. In such analyses, a key practical challenge is the presence of ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 624432fdbc45cd0f3f2e2237b6b375e7</guid><pubDate> Sun, 30 Jun 2024 02:24:22 -0400</pubDate><title>借用子集之间信息的篮子试验中的贝叶斯样本量确定</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/24/4/1000/6673175?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Basket trials are increasingly used for the simultaneous evaluation of a new treatment in various patient subgroups under one overarching protocol. We propose a Bayesian approach to sample size determination in basket trials that permit borrowing of information between commensurate subsets. Specifically, we consider a ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 3b19efcf10fb3b12d2bbfbcd520d46f2</guid><pubDate> Mon, 15 Jul 2024 02:28:19 -0400</pubDate><title>多级聚类数据的边际结构模型</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/23/4/1056/6651616?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Marginal structural models (MSMs), which adopt inverse probability treatment weighting in the estimating equations, are powerful tools to estimate the causal effects of time-varying exposures in the presence of time-dependent confounders. Motivated by the Conservation of Hearing Study (CHEARS) Audiology Assessment Arm ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> e941254572c63405dddeafa8a23aa2b5</guid><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jun 2024 10:15:06 -0400</pubDate><title> DifferentialRegulation：贝叶斯分层方法来识别差异调节基因</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/advance-article/doi/10.1093/biostatistics/kxae017/7695436?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Although transcriptomics data is typically used to analyze mature spliced mRNA, recent attention has focused on jointly investigating spliced and unspliced (or precursor-) mRNA, which can be used to study gene regulation and changes in gene expression production. Nonetheless, most methods for spliced/unspliced inference ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item></channel></rss>