<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><atom:link href="https://rsseverything.com/feed/5a44e712-2dce-412c-8683-f6fa58f0280c.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>高影响力研究-生物统计学</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/pages/highly_cited_articles <description><![CDATA[Explore a collection of the most read and most cited articles making an impact in Biostatistics published within the past two years.]]></description><lastbuilddate> 2024 年 11 月 20 日星期三 21:57:37 -0500</lastbuilddate><generator> RSS 一切</generator><ttl>360</ttl><item><guid ispermalink="false"> c81a9bf044eec983dbdc2ea6408e6962</guid><pubDate> Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:22:57 -0400</pubDate><title> googletag.cmd.push(function () { googletag.display(&#39;adBlockHeader&#39;); });</title><link/> #skipNav&quot; class=&quot;skipnav <description><![CDATA[In the analysis of single-cell RNA sequencing data, researchers often characterize the variation between cells by estimating a latent variable, such as cell type or pseudotime, representing some aspect of the cell’s state. They then test each gene for association with the estimated latent variable. If the same data are ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 6913c4e80ddb13a70ce9f809dab09386</guid><pubDate> Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:22:48 -0400</pubDate><title> DeLIVR：一种 IV 回归的深度学习方法，用于测试全转录组关联研究中的非线性因果效应</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/25/2/468/6968926?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Transcriptome-wide association studies (TWAS) have been increasingly applied to identify (putative) causal genes for complex traits and diseases. TWAS can be regarded as a two-sample two-stage least squares method for instrumental variable (IV) regression for causal inference. The standard TWAS (called TWAS-L) only ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 3b23310f917a4d2bdba06397ba6ba316</guid><pubDate> Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:22:37 -0400</pubDate><title>使用集成嵌套拉普拉斯近似对多元纵向和生存数据的联合模型进行快速灵活的推理</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/25/2/429/7235825?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Modeling longitudinal and survival data jointly offers many advantages such as addressing measurement error and missing data in the longitudinal processes, understanding and quantifying the association between the longitudinal markers and the survival events, and predicting the risk of events based on the longitudinal ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 94c40e448780a2a4dbbfda0bc93907d0</guid><pubDate> Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:22:28 -0400</pubDate><title>模糊聚类随机试验和观察性研究：针对二次抽样、缺失和少数独立单位的两阶段 TMLE</title><link/> https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/25/3/599/7235826?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Cluster randomized trials (CRTs) often enroll large numbers of participants; yet due to resource constraints, only a subset of participants may be selected for outcome assessment, and those sampled may not be representative of all cluster members. Missing data also present a challenge: if sampled individuals with measured ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 0a9828cff871856b3f2f5f817b10077f</guid><pubDate> Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:22:21 -0400</pubDate><title>平台研究中代孕的灵活评估</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/25/1/220/6968929?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Trial-level surrogates are useful tools for improving the speed and cost effectiveness of trials but surrogates that have not been properly evaluated can cause misleading results. The evaluation procedure is often contextual and depends on the type of trial setting. There have been many proposed methods for trial-level ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> fe9acaaf029b24d57dce05f60b47d36c</guid><pubDate> Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:22:16 -0400</pubDate><title>使用贝叶斯方法估算 COVID-19 发病率和感染死亡率</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/25/2/354/7070649?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Naive estimates of incidence and infection fatality rates (IFR) of coronavirus disease 2019 suffer from a variety of biases, many of which relate to preferential testing. This has motivated epidemiologists from around the globe to conduct serosurveys that measure the immunity of individuals by testing for the presence of ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 2273d2bd780d6b90749c0b8d1e4fba47</guid><pubDate> Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:22:06 -0400</pubDate><title>台湾呼吸系统疾病绘图的时空变异系数模型</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/25/1/40/6885106?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Respiratory diseases have been global public health problems for a long time. In recent years, air pollutants as important risk factors have drawn lots of attention. In this study, we investigate the influence of $\pm2.5$ (particulate matters in diameter less than 2.5 ${\rm{\mu }} m$ ) on hospital visit rates for ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> c26ab5d54d6d20af9175f5069464b31c</guid><pubDate> Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:22:13 -0400</pubDate><title>因果解释荟萃分析中系统性缺失数据</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/25/2/289/7091872?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Causally interpretable meta-analysis combines information from a collection of randomized controlled trials to estimate treatment effects in a target population in which experimentation may not be possible but from which covariate information can be obtained. In such analyses, a key practical challenge is the presence of ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> ea66968c1a1a378caed2fad6a358c701</guid><pubDate> Fri, 08 Nov 2024 21:43:56 -0500</pubDate><title>在纵向和事件时间数据联合分析中对生物标志物变异性进行建模</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/25/2/577/7179960?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[The role of visit-to-visit variability of a biomarker in predicting related disease has been recognized in medical science. Existing measures of biological variability are criticized for being entangled with random variability resulted from measurement error or being unreliable due to limited measurements per individual. ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 4d164d9a41d00e7174072bb3cbc4ae8d</guid><pubDate> Sat, 09 Nov 2024 11:23:36 -0500</pubDate><title>具有非微分测量误差的多种环境暴露的多重插补</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/25/2/306/7179961?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Measurement error is common in environmental epidemiologic studies, but methods for correcting measurement error in regression models with multiple environmental exposures as covariates have not been well investigated. We consider a multiple imputation approach, combining external or internal calibration samples that ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 4d2e65a7b2eaa067b6f537d16cbbfd65</guid><pubDate> Sun, 03 Nov 2024 20:43:30 -0500</pubDate><title>生命史研究中的选择过程、可运输性和故障时间分析</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/advance-article/doi/10.1093/biostatistics/kxae039/7845921?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[In life history analysis of data from cohort studies, it is important to address the process by which participants are identified and selected. Many health studies select or enrol individuals based on whether they have experienced certain health related events, for example, disease diagnosis or some complication from ...


    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item></channel></rss>