<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><atom:link href="https://rsseverything.com/feed/5a44e712-2dce-412c-8683-f6fa58f0280c.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><title>高影响力研究-生物统计学</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/pages/highly_cited_articles <description><![CDATA[Explore a collection of the most read and most cited articles making an impact in Biostatistics published within the past two years.]]></description><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 12 月 2 日，星期六 02:24:20 +0000</lastbuilddate><generator> RSS 一切</generator><ttl>360</ttl><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 6a06e64acc73ae5e6ca22115b4bad395</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 01:12:04 +0000</pubDate><title></title><link/> #skipNav&quot; class=&quot;skipnav <description><![CDATA[Cluster randomized trials (CRTs) randomly assign an intervention to groups of individuals (e.g., clinics or communities) and measure outcomes on individuals in those groups. While offering many advantages, this experimental design introduces challenges that are only partially addressed by existing analytic approaches. ...

    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> b75a4733a705e0154b4ff22ddd50a31d</guid><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 06:21:37 +0000</pubDate><title>克服两步批量效应校正对基因表达估计和推断的影响...</title><link/> https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/24/3/635/6459158?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Nonignorable technical variation is commonly observed across data from multiple experimental runs, platforms, or studies. These so-called batch effects can lead to difficulty in merging data from multiple sources, as they can severely bias the outcome of the analysis. Many groups have developed approaches for removing ...

    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 9db0cb802bcc4addc9f8d319c98202e1</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 01:11:54 +0000</pubDate><title>评估微生物组数据的可重复性</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/23/4/1099/6490209?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[High-throughput sequencing is widely used to study microbial communities. However, choice of laboratory protocol is known to affect the resulting microbiome data, which has an unquantified impact on many comparisons between communities of scientific interest. We propose a novel approach to evaluating replicability in ...

    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 6443b1e85e617bb783c17b666148c2bd</guid><pubDate> Thu, 19 Oct 2023 16:22:11 +0000</pubDate><title>设计三水平整群随机试验来评估治疗效果异质性</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/24/4/833/6647928?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Cluster randomized trials often exhibit a three-level structure with participants nested in subclusters such as health care providers, and subclusters nested in clusters such as clinics. While the average treatment effect has been the primary focus in planning three-level randomized trials, interest is growing in ...

    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 11b3b89aaed141855fed8ed9d1b75002</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 01:11:30 +0000</pubDate><title>半竞争风险数据的因果推断</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/23/4/1115/6490206?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[The causal effects of Apolipoprotein E $\epsilon4$ allele (APOE) on late-onset Alzheimer’s disease (AD) and death are complicated to define because AD may occur under one intervention but not under the other, and because AD occurrence may affect age of death. In this article, this dual outcome scenario is studied using the ...

    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> e20e3173e1734a1f7d2070f7e52e79eb</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 01:11:42 +0000</pubDate><title>用于分析针对妇女的犯罪的多元贝叶斯时空 P 样条模型</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/24/3/562/6484578?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Univariate spatio-temporal models for areal count data have received great attention in recent years for estimating risks. However, models for studying multivariate responses are less commonly used mainly due to the computational burden. In this article, multivariate spatio-temporal P-spline models are proposed to study ...

    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 1b3ad46128587fe55a9f806994483be3</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 01:11:26 +0000</pubDate><title>灵活的参数加速失效时间模型以及时间相关加速的扩展...</title><link/> https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/24/3/811/6593847?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Accelerated failure time (AFT) models are used widely in medical research, though to a much lesser extent than proportional hazards models. In an AFT model, the effect of covariates act to accelerate or decelerate the time to event of interest, that is, shorten or extend the time to event. Commonly used parametric AFT ...

    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> c29878990976b4c88c66872bd58e79c8</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 01:11:23 +0000</pubDate><title>疫苗在某个时间点的功效</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/24/3/603/6549823?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Vaccine trials are generally designed to assess efficacy on clinical disease. The vaccine effect on infection, while important both as a proxy for transmission and to describe a vaccine’s entire effects, requires frequent (e.g., twice a week) longitudinal sampling to capture all infections. Such sampling may not always be ...

    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> bb249b337f02a4bb89bd6840dcecbacf</guid><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 01:11:18 +0000</pubDate><title>用于从单细胞 RNA-seq 数据注释细胞类型的概率基因表达条形码</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/23/4/1150/6622011?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Single-cell RNA sequencing (scRNA-seq) quantifies gene expression for individual cells in a sample, which allows distinct cell-type populations to be identified and characterized. An important step in many scRNA-seq analysis pipelines is the annotation of cells into known cell types. While this can be achieved using ...

    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 156fa563237a4ce8e270d2668c927b48</guid><pubDate> Sun, 19 Nov 2023 01:19:36 +0000</pubDate><title>评估保护的免疫相关性的受控效应方法</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/article/24/4/850/7320953?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[An immune correlate of risk (CoR) is an immunologic biomarker in vaccine recipients associated with an infectious disease clinical endpoint. An immune correlate of protection (CoP) is a CoR that can be used to reliably predict vaccine efficacy (VE) against the clinical endpoint and hence is accepted as a surrogate endpoint ...

    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item><item><guid ispermalink="false"> 9f1a105d74dae3f3226f1544ccf8aebe</guid><pubDate> Mon, 06 Nov 2023 01:14:57 +0000</pubDate><title>通过基因和基因组系统发育分析微生物进化</title><link/>https://academic.oup.com/biostatistics/advance-article/doi/10.1093/biostatistics/kxad025/7332152?searchresult=1 <description><![CDATA[Microbiome scientists critically need modern tools to explore and analyze microbial evolution. Often this involves studying the evolution of microbial genomes as a whole. However, different genes in a single genome can be subject to different evolutionary pressures, which can result in distinct gene-level evolutionary ...

    <br/><p><sub><i>-- 由<a href="https://rsseverything.com">RssEverything</a>服务提供</i></sub></p>]]>;</description></item></channel></rss>