<feed xml:lang="zh-CN" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<id>https://newapps.f-droid.othing.xyz/new_apps.zh-CN.xml</id>
<title>New apps on F-Droid (zh-CN)</title>
<updated>2024-03-24T08:42:50.695154+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>yzqzss</name>
<email>yzqzss@yandex.com</email>
</author>
<link href="https://newapps.f-droid.othing.xyz/new_apps.zh-CN.xml" rel="self"/>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/" rel="alternate"/>
<generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="1.0.0">python-feedgen</generator>
<subtitle>New apps on F-Droid (zh-CN)</subtitle>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/nl.moeilijkedingen.jellyfinaudioplayer/</id>
<title>Fintunes</title>
<updated>2024-03-18T18:46:16+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">Fintunes 是 Jellyfin 媒体系统的流式音频播放器。 它具有华丽的界面，可让您轻松播放自己喜欢的音乐。 您可以在整个音乐库中搜索任何曲目，或者只是使用您之前在 Jellyfin 中创建的播放列表轻松一点。 所有曲目都直接以最高质量从您的 Jellyfin 库中流式传输。 流媒体并不总是一种选择？ Jellyfin 库中的任何曲目都可以下载和离线播放。&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/nl.moeilijkedingen.jellyfinaudioplayer/"/>
<summary>Jellyfin 的流媒体音频播放器</summary>
<published>2024-03-18T18:46:16+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/ie.delilahsthings.soothingloop/</id>
<title>Soothing Noise Player</title>
<updated>2024-03-18T18:42:38+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>ljmc2000</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Intended to be an android port of &lt;a href="https://github.com/rafaelmardojai/blanket">;Blanket&lt;/a>;.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Features:&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;	&lt;li>;Play any combination of 15 calming noises on loop mixed at volumes of your chosing&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;	&lt;li>;Import custom audio assets&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;	&lt;li>;Save your favorite combinations and load them later&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;	&lt;li>;Start default profile on launch (optional)&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Based on &lt;a href="https://github.com/rafaelmardojai/blanket">;Blanket&lt;/a>;, available on &lt;a href="https://flathub.org/apps/com.rafaelmardojai.Blanket">;flathub&lt;/a>;.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/ie.delilahsthings.soothingloop/"/>
<summary>Play soothing sound effects to help you relax and drown out background noise.</summary>
<published>2024-03-18T18:42:38+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.codeberg.genericpers0n.soundrecorderplus/</id>
<title>Sound Recorder Plus</title>
<updated>2024-03-16T14:51:58+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Avery King</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Sound Recorder Plus is a free and open source sound recorder for Android based on Sound Recorder. It has the following features:&lt;br>;&lt;br>;* Easy recording. Just hit the record button, hit stop when finished, and you're done!&lt;br>;* Recording management. Manage your recordings straight in the app with no hassle.&lt;br>;* High quality recording. Record in CD-quality and share with your friends.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Sound Recorder Plus also has the following improvements over its original counterpart:&lt;br>;&lt;br>;* Support for modern versions of Android. Android 7.0 or later is required.&lt;br>;* High quality recording. This option is enabled by default.&lt;br>;* Improved RTL support. The app now fully adapts to languages with an RTL layout.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.codeberg.genericpers0n.soundrecorderplus/"/>
<summary>A basic sound recorder app for Android.</summary>
<published>2024-03-16T14:51:58+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/io.gitlab.selosh.gametrader/</id>
<title>Game Trader</title>
<updated>2024-03-16T14:48:38+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Saladin Shaban</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Get notified of messages and trade offers on SteamTrades.com&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/io.gitlab.selosh.gametrader/"/>
<summary>Notifications for SteamTrades.com</summary>
<published>2024-03-16T14:48:38+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/gallery.memories/</id>
<title>Memories: Photo Management for Nextcloud</title>
<updated>2024-03-16T14:46:03+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Varun Patil</name>
</author>
<content type="html">🎁 Features&lt;br>;&lt;br>;    📸 Timeline: Sort photos and videos by date taken, parsed from Exif data.&lt;br>;    ⏪ Rewind: Jump to any time in the past instantly and relive your memories.&lt;br>;    🤖 AI Tagging: Group photos by people and objects, powered by recognize and facerecognition.&lt;br>;    🖼️ Albums: Create albums to group photos and videos together. Then share these albums with others.&lt;br>;    🫱🏻‍🫲🏻 External Sharing: Share photos and videos with people outside of your Nextcloud instance.&lt;br>;    📱 Mobile Support: Work from any device, of any shape and size through the web app.&lt;br>;    ✏️ Edit Metadata: Edit dates and other metadata on photos quickly and in bulk.&lt;br>;    📦 Archive: Store photos you don't want to see in your timeline in a separate folder.&lt;br>;    📹 Video Transcoding: Transcode videos and use HLS for maximal performance.&lt;br>;    🗺️ Map: View your photos on a map, tagged with accurate reverse geocoding.&lt;br>;    📦 Migration: Migrate easily from Nextcloud Photos and Google Takeout.&lt;br>;    ⚡️ Performance: Do all this very fast.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;For automatic uploads, you can use the official Nextcloud mobile apps. &lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/gallery.memories/"/>
<summary>Fast, modern and advanced photo management suite. Runs as a Nextcloud app.</summary>
<published>2024-03-16T14:46:03+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/dev.j7126.who_goes_first/</id>
<title>Who Goes First?</title>
<updated>2024-03-16T14:43:38+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">Don't know how to decide who goes first in a game?&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Get a random funny "who goes first" condition, from popular tabletop games.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Contains rules from over 150 games.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Conditions like:&lt;br>; - "Who last fed a duck?"&lt;br>; - "Who broke the law most recently?"&lt;br>; - "Who last visited an island?"&lt;br>; - "Who has the most facial hair?"&lt;br>; - And over 150 more.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/dev.j7126.who_goes_first/"/>
<summary>Random funny "who goes first" rules from popular tabletop games!</summary>
<published>2024-03-16T14:43:38+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.w2sv.filenavigator/</id>
<title>File Navigator</title>
<updated>2024-03-16T14:39:29+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Janek Zangenberg</name>
</author>
<content type="html">&lt;b>;Welcome to File Navigator - Your Ultimate File Sorting Solution!&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Are you tired of cluttered files on your device? Seeking a streamlined way to organize and manage them? Look no further! File Navigator is here to transform your file management experience.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;Key Features:&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🔍 &lt;b>;File Type Customization: File Navigator puts you in control. Select the specific file types you want to navigate, including Images, Videos, Audio, Text, APKs, PDFs, and Archives.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;📁 &lt;b>;Effortless File Organization:&lt;/b>; Configure the app to match your preferences. File Navigator allows you to define where different file types should be stored, ensuring they end up in the right place every time.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;📬 &lt;b>;Instant Notifications:&lt;/b>; When new files of your chosen file types are detected in your system, File Navigator sends you instant notifications. No more surprises - you'll always be up-to-date.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🚀 &lt;b>;Seamless File Movement:&lt;/b>; With a simple tap from the notification, you can select the destination folder for the new file. No more manual searching and sorting.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🔁 &lt;b>;Auto-Move Functionality:&lt;/b>; Streamline your workflow further! If you receive multiple files of the same type, activate the auto-move feature. File Navigator automatically places them in the folder you previously selected.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🛡️ &lt;b>;Precise Permissions:&lt;/b>; To deliver these exceptional features, File Navigator requests the 'access to manage all files' permission. Rest assured, this permission is solely used to move files you explicitly command to be moved.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;📱 &lt;b>;Simplify Your Digital Life:&lt;/b>; File Navigator is the ultimate solution to keep your files organized and readily accessible. Enjoy a clutter-free device and manage your files with ease.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Don't let file chaos overwhelm you. Say goodbye to clutter and embrace the power of precise file management!&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.w2sv.filenavigator/"/>
<summary>The missing link between Android and a well-structured file system</summary>
<published>2024-03-16T14:39:29+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.timebinding.manhoodofhumanity/</id>
<title>Manhood of Humanity</title>
<updated>2024-03-16T14:38:49+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">&lt;b>;Manhood of Humanity, Second Edition A. Korzybski&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;This work began with a functional definition of &lt;b>;'man'&lt;/b>;, formulated in 1921, based on an analysis of uniquely human potentials; specifically, that each generation can start where the previous one left off. I called this characteristic the &lt;b>;'time-binding'&lt;/b>; capacity .... We no longer have to blind ourselves to the old dogmas about the &lt;b>;'immutability of human nature'&lt;/b>; because we have discovered that we &lt;b>;can change it&lt;/b>;. We should realize our human potentials so that we can go to the future with some hope. Alfred Korzybski.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;General Semantics (GS)&lt;/b>; was developed by Alfred Korzybski, a Polish engineer who settled in the United States after World War I. The death and destruction of war horrified him and prompted him to search for an answer to the question of how humans have been able to advance technologically so far, yet are unable to put their relationships in order. After researching this question for more than a decade, he formulated a general semantics, which he presented most fully in his book Science and Sanity (1933).&lt;br>;&lt;br>;«&lt;b>;General semantics&lt;/b>; is not any kind of 'philosophy', 'psychology', or 'logic'. It is a new extensional discipline through which we explain and learn how to apply our nervous systems most effectively.» - A. Korzybski &lt;br>;&lt;br>;«In &lt;b>;general semantics&lt;/b>;, we do not 'preach' 'morality' or 'ethics' per se, but teach students awareness of abstraction, awareness of multi-order evaluation mechanisms, relationship orientation, etc., which lead to cortico-thalamic integration, and as a result 'morality', 'ethics', awareness of social responsibility, etc., follow &lt;b>;automatically&lt;/b>;. » - A. Korzybski&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Alfred Korzybski was born in the late 19th century into a noble family living in the Russian-occupied part of politically divided Poland. "I was born silent," he wrote - an observer looking around with an interest in what was happening. From an early age, he realized his calling to "solve problems." His father, an engineer by profession, fostered in him a respect for math and physics, and their practical applications. (Alfred later studied engineering himself.) He grew up a Polish patriot under the oppression of the Tsarist dictatorship. While serving in Russian army intelligence, &lt;b>;he witnessed the horrors of World War I&lt;/b>; on the eastern front. By then, having moved to North America, he had witnessed the reckless behavior of people &lt;b>;(including himself)&lt;/b>; for half his life. "&lt;b>;I was simply tired of human stupidity. I didn't care about anything else&lt;/b>;."&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Korzybski spent the rest of his days in a purposeful search and attempt to realize his life's dream - to promote harmony among people by understanding and solving the problems of human stupidity (preventable inadequate evaluation) and its consequences. What is it that human beings possess that makes them make tremendous progress in some areas (math, science, applied technology), but come to such a decline in others? Could we find a way to &lt;b>;prevent&lt;/b>; at least some of the human ills and societal problems that Korzybski has seen? Would we have been able to update our maps (both in the narrow and broad sense of the term), including maps of ourselves, to avoid unnecessary misunderstandings and conflicts between people in society? Experience convinced him that people should develop their thinking abilities (which for Korzybski did not exist separately from their emotional life). He was troubled by the lack of a way to help thinking in a purposeful and systematic way. &lt;b>;("Where are we taught how to think? Nowhere.")&lt;/b>; His knowledge of &lt;b>;science and mathematics&lt;/b>; also convinced him to &lt;b>;try to develop a method of thinking for everyday life based on these disciplines&lt;/b>;. Korzybski conducted research on the 'strange' hypothesis - unconscious factors of personal and social adaptation (sanity) are realized in the professional behavior - including language - of scientists and mathema</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.timebinding.manhoodofhumanity/"/>
<summary>Materials on general-semantics. An Introduction to Non-Aristotelian Systems and </summary>
<published>2024-03-16T14:38:49+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.thatsmanmeet.clipboardcleaner/</id>
<title>Clipboard Cleaner</title>
<updated>2024-03-16T14:38:45+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Manmeet Singh</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Clipboard Cleaner android app for showing and cleaning clipboard. This app have a simple interface with only two buttons, Show Clipboard and Clean Clipboard. Both shows a small message (Toast) at the bottom with one showing the last copied text in clipboard while other clears the clipboard completely.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;p>;Note&lt;/p>;&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;On some android devices the clipboard cleaning might not work as some vendors implement their own method of managing clipboards.&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Also if you're using a keyboard app with clipboard manager turned on (e.g. GBoard with it's own clipboard) then this app will not be able to clean that history as it belongs to the keyboard app itself and it have to be cleared manually by the user or you can disable the keyboard's own implementation of clipboard manager.&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.thatsmanmeet.clipboardcleaner/"/>
<summary>An android app for showing and cleaning clipboard.</summary>
<published>2024-03-16T14:38:45+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/de.hbch.traewelling/</id>
<title>Träwelldroid</title>
<updated>2024-03-13T14:59:04+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Jonas Heubuch</name>
</author>
<content type="html">&lt;p>;&lt;i>;Träwelldroid&lt;/i>; ist ein kostenloser Check-In-Service zur Aufzeichnung Deiner Fahrten im ÖPNV. Zur Nutzung dieser App ist ein Konto bei Träwelling erforderlich.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;Mit dieser App kannst du:&lt;/p>;&lt;ul>;&lt;li>;deutschlandweit und in einigen Ländern Europas in deine Reisen im ÖPNV und ÖPFV einchecken&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;deine Check-Ins auf Twitter und Mastodon teilen&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;in Events der Träwelling-Community einchecken&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;Statistiken bezüglich deiner Fahrten ansehen&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;Fahrten deiner Freunde ansehen und gemeinsam mit ihnen einchecken&lt;/li>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;p>;Diese App ist ein Community-Projekt und steht in keinem offiziellen Zusammenhang zu Träwelling selbst.&lt;/p>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/de.hbch.traewelling/"/>
<summary>Free check-in service for recording journeys in public transport</summary>
<published>2024-03-13T14:59:04+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.rk.xededitor/</id>
<title>Xed Editor</title>
<updated>2024-03-16T14:37:39+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">&lt;p>;&lt;i>;Xed Editor&lt;/i>; is a versatile text editor designed specifically for Android devices, offering users the ability to create, edit, and manage their text files with ease on their mobile devices.&lt;/p>;&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.rk.xededitor/"/>
<summary>Advanced Text Editor for Android</summary>
<published>2024-03-13T14:55:40+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.danilkinkin.buckwheat/</id>
<title>Buckwheat: Budget manager</title>
<updated>2024-03-13T14:49:11+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Danil Зakhvatkin</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Buckwheat is an app that helps you spend money wisely. Writing down each spending sobers the mind and gives you an idea of how much and how you can spend.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Are you going on a business trip or vacation? Buckwheat helps you save money during your trip.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.danilkinkin.buckwheat/"/>
<summary>App that helps you spend money wisely</summary>
<published>2024-03-13T14:49:11+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/yetzio.yetcalc/</id>
<title>yetCalc</title>
<updated>2024-03-09T17:09:05+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Yet-Zio</name>
</author>
<content type="html">yetCalc is a Calculator with basic and scientific calculation features, a unit converter and a programmer mode. The design is loosely based on Google's Calculator and tries to address its problems.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;HINT: Use landscape orientation to access scientific mode.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Features: &lt;br>;• Progressive Calculations&lt;br>;• Scientific Mode with trigonometric, hyperbolic and inverse functions, calculus and iterated operators, much more.&lt;br>;• Unit Converter&lt;br>;• Programmer Mode with number systems and logical operations.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;NOTE: Internet connection is used for currency conversions and nothing else.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/yetzio.yetcalc/"/>
<summary>Progressive calculator, converter and much more.</summary>
<published>2024-03-09T17:09:05+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.vinaygopinath.launchchat/</id>
<title>Launch Chat</title>
<updated>2024-03-09T17:06:08+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Vinay Gopinath</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Features&lt;br>;* Avoid granting WhatsApp, Signal and Telegram access to your contacts&lt;br>;* Start a one-off conversation with a phone number without cluttering up your contacts&lt;br>;* Click on a phone number in any app or website and share it with "Launch Chat" to start a WhatsApp/Signal/Telegram conversation.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.vinaygopinath.launchchat/"/>
<summary>Start a WhatsApp, Signal or Telegram chat without saving a number as a contact</summary>
<published>2024-03-09T17:06:08+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/info.metadude.android.fossgis.schedule/</id>
<title>FOSSGIS 2024 Schedule</title>
<updated>2024-03-09T16:54:43+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Tobias Preuss</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Programm zur FOSSGIS-Konferenz am 20. - 23. März 2024 in Hamburg&lt;br>;&lt;br>;https://www.fossgis-konferenz.de&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;i>;Die FOSSGIS-Konferenz ist im D-A-CH-Raum die führende Konferenz&lt;br>;für Freie und Open Source Software für Geoinformationssysteme sowie&lt;br>;für die Themen Open Data und OpenStreetMap.&lt;/i>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;Funktionen&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;* Tagesüberblick über alle Programmpunkte&lt;br>;* Beschreibung von Veranstaltungen lesen&lt;br>;* Veranstaltungen in persönlicher Favoritenliste verwalten&lt;br>;* Favoritenliste exportieren&lt;br>;* Alarm für Veranstaltungen setzen&lt;br>;* Veranstaltungen in Kalender eintragen&lt;br>;* Link zu Veranstaltungen mit anderen teilen&lt;br>;* Programmänderungen einsehen&lt;br>;* Veranstaltungen bewerten&lt;br>;* Integration mit dem Helfersystem, https://helfen.fossgis.de (siehe Einstellungen in der App)&lt;br>;* Integration mit Chaosflix https://github.com/NiciDieNase/chaosflix - Android App für https://media.ccc.de, teile Fahrplan-Favoriten mit Chaosflix und importiere sie als Bookmarks&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🔤 &lt;b>;Unterstützte Sprachen&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;(Programmtexte ausgenommen)&lt;br>;* Dänisch&lt;br>;* Deutsch&lt;br>;* Englisch&lt;br>;* Finnisch&lt;br>;* Französisch&lt;br>;* Italienisch&lt;br>;* Japanisch&lt;br>;* Litauisch&lt;br>;* Niederländisch&lt;br>;* Polnisch&lt;br>;* Portugiesisch&lt;br>;* Russisch&lt;br>;* Spanisch&lt;br>;* Schwedisch&lt;br>;* Türkisch&lt;br>;&lt;br>;💡 Inhaltliche Fragen zum Programm kann nur das FOSSGIS-Team&lt;br>;beantworten. Diese App stellt lediglich die Programmpunkte zur Verfügung.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;💣 Fehlerberichte sind herzlich willkommen, aber achte darauf, dass&lt;br>;du erklärst, wie man den Fehler reproduzieren kann. Der Issue-Tracker&lt;br>;findet sich hier: https://github.com/EventFahrplan/EventFahrplan/issues&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🏆 Die App basiert auf der &lt;b>;EventFahrplan-App&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;https://f-droid.org/packages/info.metadude.android.congress.schedule/&lt;br>;für den Kongress des Chaos Computer Clubs. Der Quellcode der Anwendung ist auf GitHub&lt;br>;https://github.com/johnjohndoe/CampFahrplan/tree/fossgis-2024 zu finden.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🎨 FOSSGIS-Logo-Design: FOSSGIS e.V. bzw. dimdle&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/info.metadude.android.fossgis.schedule/"/>
<summary>FOSSGIS 会议的会议应用</summary>
<published>2024-03-09T16:54:43+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/fr.smarquis.soundquicksettings/</id>
<title>Sound Quick Settings</title>
<updated>2024-03-09T16:53:55+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Simon Marquis</name>
</author>
<content type="html">1. Add the Tile in the Quick Settings panel.&lt;br>;2. Tap the Tile to show the volume slider.&lt;br>;3. Long press the Tile to open the Sound panel.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;u>;Note:&lt;/u>; Don't look for a launcher icon, this app only provides a Quick Settings Tile.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Open Source project hosted on GitHub: https://github.com/SimonMarquis/Android-SoundQuickSettings</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/fr.smarquis.soundquicksettings/"/>
<summary>A simple Quick Settings Tile to control the sound volume.</summary>
<published>2024-03-09T16:53:55+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.corphish.quicktools/</id>
<title>Text Tools</title>
<updated>2024-03-16T14:30:43+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Avinaba Dalal</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Collection of useful text related tools that can be accessed from the context menu that appears on text selection. The feature list will keep on growing. Let me know if you have any ideas.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Current Features&lt;br>;1. Text unsaved numbers in WhatsApp - Often we find ourselves needing to text/send file/share location to someone for temporary purposes (if you ask me, I face this a lot in situations where I go to a printing centre where they ask me to share the file that I want to print over WhatsApp, so I have to save their contact, refresh my WhatsApp contact list and then send them). Having a context menu option to directly open a WhatsApp chat from their phone number would save a lot of time and keep your phonebook clean, right?&lt;br>;2. Evaluate mathematical expressions inline - We may often find ourselves to mathematically calculate something while texting someone (probably while making plans). Having an option to perform math calculations in line without needing to open calculator could save time.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Where are screenshots?&lt;br>;The app adds capabilities to text selection wherever supported in the Android System, there is nothing much to do inside the app, hence very less screenshots.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Installation Warning&lt;br>;While installing the app (you have to sideload), Google Play may block the installation saying it has never seen the app before. While it is true (from Google Play POV), kindly proceed with installing the app. If you have doubts about the app being malicious, you are free to verify the same from the source code (it would not be open-source if the app was malicious in the first place, right?).</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.corphish.quicktools/"/>
<summary>Useful text related functions that can be done on the selected text</summary>
<published>2024-03-09T16:37:51+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/space.irex.mobile/</id>
<title>IREX Mobile App</title>
<updated>2024-03-05T18:47:13+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>IREX</name>
</author>
<content type="html">IREX mobile application.&lt;br>;This application facilitates interactions between IREX community members (candidates, representatives, project leaders, workspace tenants, etc.)</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/space.irex.mobile/"/>
<summary>IREX mobile application</summary>
<published>2024-03-05T18:47:13+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/io.github.sspanak.tt9/</id>
<title>Traditional T9</title>
<updated>2024-03-05T18:36:14+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Dimo Karaivanov</name>
</author>
<content type="html">A T9 keyboard for devices with a hardware keypad. It supports predictive text typing in 20+ languages, configurable hotkeys, and an on-screen keypad for touchscreen-only phones, bringing an old-school Nokia experience to modern Android devices. Best of all, it doesn't spy on you.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Supported languages: Arabic, Bulgarian, Danish, Dutch, English, Finnish, French, German, Greek, Hebrew, Indonesian, Italian, Norwegian, Polish, Portugues (European and Brazilian), Romanian, Russian, Spanish, Swedish, Ukrainian, Yiddish.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;IMPORTANT! If you have the Github or the IzzyOnDroid version, you must uninstall it, before installing this one. Android does not allow installing the same app from different source for security reasons.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/io.github.sspanak.tt9/"/>
<summary>A T9 keyboard for devices with a hardware keypad.</summary>
<published>2024-03-05T18:36:14+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/io.github.aloussase.booksdownloader/</id>
<title>Alexandria</title>
<updated>2024-03-13T15:04:25+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Alexander Goussas</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Alexandria is an open-source application for downloading and converting EBooks.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Features:&lt;br>;&lt;br>;* Search for your favorite titles and download them&lt;br>;* Can't find your favorite book in the right format? No problem, builtin EBook&lt;br>;  converter&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Download sources:&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Alexandria uses the following download sources:&lt;br>;&lt;br>;* Libgen (http://libgen.is/) which is considered non-free for being a shadow library&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Ebook conversion sources:&lt;br>;&lt;br>;* Alexandria API (https://alexandria.up.railway.app) which is a proprietary custom-made source&lt;br>;&lt;br>;I will consider open-sourcing the Alexandria API once its mature enough.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Source Code:&lt;br>;&lt;br>;The source code for this project is available on GitHub at&lt;br>;https://github.com/aloussase/alexandria-app.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/io.github.aloussase.booksdownloader/"/>
<summary>Download and convert EBooks.</summary>
<published>2024-03-05T18:34:37+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/eth.brume.wallet/</id>
<title>Brume Wallet</title>
<updated>2024-03-13T15:02:05+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">Meet the only Ethereum wallet with maximum privacy and security.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/eth.brume.wallet/"/>
<summary>The private Ethereum wallet</summary>
<published>2024-03-05T18:33:03+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/dev.octoshrimpy.quik/</id>
<title>QUIK SMS</title>
<updated>2024-03-05T18:32:48+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>octoshrimpy</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Open source replacement to the stock SMS app on Android. A revival of QKSMS.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;QUIK is available to download from the official &lt;a href="https://github.com/octoshrimpy/quik/releases">;github releases page&lt;/a>;, but you can also keep track of updates with &lt;br>;&lt;a href="https://github.com/ImranR98/Obtainium#-obtainium">;Obtanium&lt;/a>;.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;You can chat with the community over at &lt;a href="https://matrix.to/#/#quik-sms:matrix.org">;#quik-sms:matrix.org&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/dev.octoshrimpy.quik/"/>
<summary>Open source replacement to the stock SMS app on Android. A revival of QKSMS.</summary>
<published>2024-03-05T18:32:48+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/de.z11.roboyard/</id>
<title>Roboyard</title>
<updated>2024-03-05T18:32:07+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Ruben Barkow-Kuder</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Ein einfaches, aber herausforderndes Denkspiel.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Du steuerst vier Roboter in einem 16x16 Felder großen Garten. Das Ziel ist es, einen bestimmten Roboter zum Ziel zu lenken. Die Roboter bewegen sich, bis sie entweder an eine Hecke oder einen anderen Roboter stoßen.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Das Besondere an dieser App ist der automatische Lösungsfindungsalgorythmus, der dir Hinweise und auch die optimale Lösung mit den wenigsten Zügen anzeigen kann.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Kannst du die Lösung mit den wenigsten Zügen finden?&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Dieses Spiel ist Open Source und wird ohne Adds ausgeliefert. Inspiriert von Rasender Roboter&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Quellcode unter https://roboyard.z11.de/</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/de.z11.roboyard/"/>
<summary>Problem-solving game - find the optimal moves to move one robot to its target</summary>
<published>2024-03-05T18:32:07+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.example.secreto/</id>
<title>Sekreto</title>
<updated>2024-03-05T18:19:26+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">The application is only in Esperanto and Russian.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.example.secreto/"/>
<summary>Kaŝu sekretan mesaĝon en teksto!</summary>
<published>2024-03-05T18:19:26+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/pl.suve.colorful.android/</id>
<title>Colorful</title>
<updated>2024-02-28T18:44:51+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>suve</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Colorful is a simple side-view shooter game, where the protagonist&lt;br>;travels a maze of caves and corridors in order to collect color artifacts.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/pl.suve.colorful.android/"/>
<summary>Simple 2D side-view shooter</summary>
<published>2024-02-28T18:44:51+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/net.leodesouza.blitz/</id>
<title>Blitz: Fischer chess clock</title>
<updated>2024-03-16T14:50:24+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">&lt;p>;&lt;b>;Features&lt;/b>;&lt;/p>;&lt;ul>;&lt;li>;Defaults to 5+3 Fischer timing (5 minutes + 3 seconds per move).&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;Total time and increment can be set by horizontal and vertical dragging.&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;The back action pauses or resets the clock.&lt;/li>;&lt;/ul>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/net.leodesouza.blitz/"/>
<summary>A minimalist Fischer chess clock for Android.</summary>
<published>2024-02-28T18:35:31+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/io.nekohasekai.sfa/</id>
<title>sing-box</title>
<updated>2024-03-13T15:05:38+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Project S</name>
</author>
<content type="html">sing-box is a fast, customizable and univsersal proxy platform that can be used to create network proxy servers, clients and transparent proxies. This app allows users to manage and use local and remote sing-box profiles and provides platform specific feature implementations such as the TUN transparent proxy implementation through the Android VpnService.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/io.nekohasekai.sfa/"/>
<summary>The universal proxy platform</summary>
<published>2024-02-28T18:33:35+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/xyz.pisoj.og.nettools/</id>
<title>OG Network Tools</title>
<updated>2024-02-24T16:26:29+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">&lt;p>;Downloads and opens &lt;strong>;instantly&lt;/strong>;, seriously it's well &lt;strong>;under 200KB!&lt;/strong>; Why? - Because today's apps tend to feel slow and janky on anything but the latest hardware, no more.&lt;/p>;&lt;br>;&lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Device support&lt;/strong>; - All devices running &lt;strong>;Android 3.0&lt;/strong>; and above are supported!&lt;/p>;&lt;br>;&lt;p>;&lt;strong>;How is is possible?&lt;/strong>; - The small size and &lt;strong>;extreme compatibility&lt;/strong>; are possible thanks to our &lt;strong>;no dependency&lt;/strong>; policy. This app literally has empty depecndecies block.&lt;/p>;&lt;br>;&lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Does it look good?&lt;/strong>; - The app uses the original andorid &lt;strong>;Holo&lt;/strong>; theme, so it's perfect if you miss &lt;strong>;good old days&lt;/strong>;, but we've also given it a &lt;strong>;modern twist&lt;/strong>; with custom implementations of UI components like floating action button for example.&lt;/p>;&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/xyz.pisoj.og.nettools/"/>
<summary>A modern network toolbox built to feel like original android apps.</summary>
<published>2024-02-24T16:26:29+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.secuso.privacyfriendlybattleship/</id>
<title>Schiffe versenken (Privacy Friendly)</title>
<updated>2024-02-24T16:23:26+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>SECUSO - Security Usability Society</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Mit der App Privacy Friendly Schiffe versenken kann man das beliebte Spiel "Schiffe versenken" bequem auf dem Smartphone spielen. Ziel des Spiels ist es, alle Schiffe des Gegners zu versenken, indem beide Spieler abwechselnd auf das Spielfeld des Gegners "schießen".&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Das Spiel bietet zwei Spielmodi:&lt;br>;- Spieler vs Computer&lt;br>;- Spieler vs Spieler&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Der Spieler kann dabei zwischen den Spielfeldgrößen 5x5 und 10x10 wählen und seine Schiffe frei platzieren. Die Anzahl der Schiffe kann vor dem Spiel selbst gewählt werden. Dabei sind Schiffe der Größen 2 (U-Boote), 3 (Zerstörer), 4 (Kreuzer) und 5 (Schlachtschiffe) möglich.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Was unterscheidet Privacy Friendly Schiffe Versenken von anderen, ähnlichen Apps?&lt;br>;&lt;br>;1. Keine Berechtigungen&lt;br>;Privacy Friendly Schiffe versenken verwendet keine Berechtigungen.&lt;br>;Zum Vergleich: Die Top Ten ähnlicher Apps, die im Google Play Store erhältlich sind, benötigt durchschnittlich 6,1 Berechtigungen (Stand: November 2017). Hierzu zählen der Zugriff auf Netzwerke, das Internet oder Standortdaten.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;2. Keine störende Werbung&lt;br>;Viele andere kostenlose Apps im Google Play Store blenden störende Werbung ein, die unter anderem auch die Akkulaufzeit verkürzt und Datenvolumen verbrauchen kann.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Die App gehört zur Gruppe der Privacy Friendly Apps, die von der Forschungsgruppe SECUSO der Technischen Universität Darmstadt entwickelt werden. Mehr Informationen unter: https://secuso.org/pfa&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.secuso.privacyfriendlybattleship/"/>
<summary>(SECUSO) Play the battleship game on your smartphone without ads or permissions</summary>
<published>2024-02-24T16:23:26+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.fossify.voicerecorder/</id>
<title>Fossify Voice Recorder</title>
<updated>2024-02-24T16:20:18+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Fossify</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Introducing Fossify Voice Recorder – where capturing crystal-clear audio and preserving precious moments is effortless and enjoyable. Seamlessly blend simplicity with functionality as you embark on a journey of seamless recording experiences tailored to your needs.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🔊 HIGH-QUALITY AUDIO CAPTURE:&lt;br>;Remember every word, every note, and every emotion with pristine audio quality. Fossify Voice Recorder empowers you to capture high-fidelity recordings effortlessly, ensuring that every detail is preserved with clarity and precision.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🎙️ VERSATILE RECORDING OPTIONS:&lt;br>;From voice memos to musical inspirations, this intuitive app transforms your device into a versatile recording studio. Explore the freedom to document your surroundings and unleash your creativity with ease.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🚀 NO-FUSS FUNCTIONALITY:&lt;br>;Enjoy a clutter-free experience with Fossify Voice Recorder. Say goodbye to unnecessary features and hello to a streamlined interface designed for intuitive navigation and seamless recording.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;📊 INTUITIVE VISUALIZATION:&lt;br>;Immerse yourself in the recording process with real-time sound volume visualization. Experience the thrill of monitoring your recordings with a sleek, interactive display that enhances your recording experience.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🔒 PRIVACY-FIRST APPROACH:&lt;br>;Rest easy knowing that your privacy is our priority. Fossify Voice Recorder operates offline, ensuring maximum privacy, security, and stability without the need for internet access. Your recordings remain confidential and under your control at all times.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🎨 CUSTOMIZABLE INTERFACE:&lt;br>;Personalize your recording experience with customizable colors and themes. Embrace the sleek elegance of material design and dark theme options, offering a visually stunning experience tailored to your preferences.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🤝 USER-FRIENDLY FEATURES:&lt;br>;Discover intuitive functionalities like customizable filename formats and practical widgets for quick recordings. With Fossify Voice Recorder, the power to record is in your hands.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🌐 AD-FREE &amp; OPEN-SOURCE:&lt;br>;Say goodbye to intrusive ads and unnecessary permissions. Fossify Voice Recorder is ad-free, fully open-source, and grants you the freedom to use the app as you please, without compromise.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Capture moments, preserve memories, and unleash your creativity with Fossify Voice Recorder. Download now and experience recording like never before.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Explore more Fossify apps: https://www.fossify.org&lt;br>;Open-Source Code: https://www.github.com/FossifyOrg&lt;br>;Join the community on Reddit: https://www.reddit.com/r/Fossify&lt;br>;Connect on Telegram: https://t.me/Fossify&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.fossify.voicerecorder/"/>
<summary>Record anything with this Open-source and Ad-free recorder</summary>
<published>2024-02-24T16:20:18+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.akanework.gramophone/</id>
<title>Gramophone</title>
<updated>2024-02-24T16:18:20+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>AkaneTan, nift4</name>
</author>
<content type="html">&lt;p>;&lt;i>;Gramophone&lt;/i>; is a sane music player built with media3 and material design library that is following android's standard strictly.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;Features&lt;/b>;&lt;/p>;&lt;ul>;&lt;li>;Up-to-date material 3 design&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;Monet themed icon on Android 12+&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;View and play your favorite music&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;Search your favourite music&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;Web streaming (coming soon!)&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;Synced lyrics&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;Manage &amp; Add your playlist&lt;/li>;&lt;/ul>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.akanework.gramophone/"/>
<summary>A sane media3-based Material3 music player that follows Android standards</summary>
<published>2024-02-24T16:18:20+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/me.x2gd4.dollphone/</id>
<title>Dollphone Icon Pack</title>
<updated>2024-03-13T15:06:28+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>HaleyW</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Dollphone is a cute icon pack that is very cute, but isn’t too hyper. The icons avoid overly saturated or dark colors, and softly bulge out the "straight" lines away from the center for a plushie-like look.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Dollphone Icon Pack is a crystallization of years of passion for the “yurukawa” aesthetic.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/me.x2gd4.dollphone/"/>
<summary>Cute icon pack that isn’t overly hyperactive</summary>
<published>2024-02-24T16:16:45+00:00</published>
</entry>
</feed>