<feed xml:lang="zh-CN" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<id>https://newapps.f-droid.othing.xyz/new_apps.zh-CN.xml</id>
<title>New apps on F-Droid (zh-CN)</title>
<updated>2025-01-07T08:40:31.437285+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>yzqzss</name>
<email>yzqzss@yandex.com</email>
</author>
<link href="https://newapps.f-droid.othing.xyz/new_apps.zh-CN.xml" rel="self"/>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/" rel="alternate"/>
<generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="1.0.0">python-feedgen</generator>
<subtitle>New apps on F-Droid (zh-CN)</subtitle>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/net.nymtech.nymvpn/</id>
<title>NymVPN：快速安全的 VPN</title>
<updated>2025-01-02T18:33:01+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">下载NymVPN，确保您的在线活动安全。&lt;br>;使用我们的VPN应用程序，您可以隐藏您的IP地址、加密您的流量、隐藏您的在线身份等。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;互联网上的许多实体都可以监视你的活动并获取你的数据。&lt;br>;政府、大型科技公司、数据经纪商、互联网服务提供商和广告商都可以试图监视你的在线活动。 最近的数据泄露丑闻清楚地表明，我们甚至不能相信传统的 VPN 公司。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;NymVPN是一种新型的VPN，其设计方式使得任何人都无法监控或记录您的在线活动，即使是我们自己。&lt;br>;我们的VPN是在一个去中心化的网络上运行的，没有受托方、集中组件或单点故障。 NymVPN 的所有功能都是以去中心化和分布式的方式执行的，不可能启用集中式日志记录。&lt;br>;我们的 VPN 通过去中心化 Mixnet 对数据进行加密并屏蔽元数据，使其免受流量分析的影响。 简而言之：我们无法记录您的活动，因此任何人都无法访问您的活动。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;但究竟什么是混合网络？ 混合网络是由以下节点组成的网络：&lt;br>;1. 接收加密流量&lt;br>;2. 混合流量&lt;br>;3. 重定向流量&lt;br>;这个过程最多进行 5 次（5 跳），让任何人都无法监控或跟踪你的在线活动。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;因此，您应该选择我们的去中心化、安全和专用 VPN&lt;br>;&lt;br>;隐私&lt;br>;我们的 dVPN 考虑到了隐私问题。 我们不存储日志（无日志政策），也不跟踪您的活动。 即使有人想从我们这里窃取您的数据，也没有什么可窃取的。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;抵制审查&lt;br>;我们的 VPN 应用程序让您的在线活动完全匿名。 我们会加密您的流量、IP 地址、位置以及一切可能被居心不良者监控的内容。 有了杀毒开关等功能，您就完全安全了。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;速度&lt;br>;由于许多额外的节点加入了 Mixnet 网络，我们的 VPN 网络速度每分钟都在增长。 此外，我们使用现代加密算法和创新协议（如 Sphinx 和 Loopix），使您的连接速度尽可能快。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;地点选择&lt;br>;使用NymVPN，您可以选择在全球数百个地点进行连接。&lt;br>;下载应用程序 -->; 选择地点 -->; 连接&lt;br>;&lt;br>;加密货币支付&lt;br>;您正在寻找一个接受加密货币支付的 VPN？ 我们就是。 我们很高兴接受加密货币付款。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;无广告&lt;br>;享受无广告的 VPN。 我们的主要目标是保护您的隐私，因此您在我们的 VPN 应用程序中看不到任何广告。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;无限使用&lt;br>;NymVPN绝不会限制您的流量，让您尽情享受互联网的乐趣。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;我们的 VPN 最受欢迎的功能：&lt;br>;- 5-hop Mixnet: 您的网络流量将被加密，并发送到混合节点，与其他流量包混合 5 次，使他人无法跟踪您的在线活动。&lt;br>;- 2-hop dVPN: 在这种情况下，您的流量会被加密并发送到 2 个混合节点进行混合。 跳数减少，速度提高。&lt;br>;- 无中心化日志：我们不存储任何活动日志，因此任何人都无法通过我们获取您的互联网活动。&lt;br>;- 退款保证：如果您对产品不满意，我们提供退款保证政策。 如果您对某些产品不满意，请发送电子邮件至 support@nymvpn.com，我们一直在寻求改进。&lt;br>;- 分割隧道：您可以轻松选择哪些应用程序通过 VPN 访问互联网，哪些应用程序直接访问互联网。&lt;br>;- 隐藏 IP：我们的 dVPN 将隐藏与您相关的所有信息，包括您的 IP 地址。&lt;br>;- 杀毒开关：我们的 VPN 专为提供隐私和安全而设计，这就是为什么在您的 VPN 连接中断时，杀毒开关会阻止您访问互联网，确保您和您的数据安全。&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/net.nymtech.nymvpn/"/>
<summary>下载我们的 VPN，让您的在线活动 100% 隐私，快速、匿名。</summary>
<published>2025-01-02T18:33:01+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/kzs.th000.tsdm_client/</id>
<title>天使动漫</title>
<updated>2025-01-02T18:32:34+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>realth000</name>
</author>
<content type="html">&lt;h3>;功能&lt;/h3>;&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;看贴&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;回帖&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;编辑帖子&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;发帖&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;登录&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;搜索&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;积分&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;购买&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;签到&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;深色模式&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;主题&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;用户信息&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;通知&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;好友&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;应用内更新&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;收藏&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;多用户&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;多语言&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/kzs.th000.tsdm_client/"/>
<summary>天使动漫论坛第三方客户端</summary>
<published>2025-01-02T18:32:30+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/de.dennisguse.opentracks.playstore/</id>
<title>OpenTracks (Reproducible build)</title>
<updated>2025-01-02T18:27:28+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>OpenTracks Team</name>
</author>
<content type="html">一款尊重您的隐私的运动追踪应用。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;健康幸福的生活总少不了各种运动和户外活动。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;使用本应用，您可以保持对您的训练数据的有效追踪，为您的健康助力。&lt;br>;本应用可以在您跑步或散步时记录数据，也可以在您骑车时作为一个大屏幕自行车电脑。&lt;br>;您可以为路上的有趣位置创建标记，还可以用图片作为标记。&lt;br>;您的数据会被详尽地记录下来，供您查阅分析。&lt;br>;您的数据只会分享给您想要分享给的人。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;* 语音播报&lt;br>;* 支持蓝牙LE传感器：心率、速度和距离（骑车）、踏频（骑车）和功率计（骑车）。&lt;br>;* 海拔增减：通过气压传感器。&lt;br>;* EGM2008 海拔显示（平均海平面以上）；导出为 WGS84。&lt;br>;* 导出路线数据，支持 KMZ（包括照片）、KML 和 GPX 格式。&lt;br>;* 不需要联网，不需要额外权限。&lt;br>;* 深色和浅色主题，跟随系统设置。&lt;br>;* 没有广告。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;本应用是开源软件&lt;br>;意味着您可以使用、学习、修改和分发本应用的源代码。&lt;br>;本应用使用 Apache 2.0 协议发布。&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/de.dennisguse.opentracks.playstore/"/>
<summary>一款尊重您的隐私的运动追踪应用。</summary>
<published>2025-01-02T18:27:28+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.github.dyhkwong.sagernet/</id>
<title>Exclave</title>
<updated>2025-01-02T18:23:46+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>dyhkwong</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Exclave is a proxy client. It is a fork of the archived SagerNet and based on a custom fork of v2ray-core. It uses plugins to support some protocols that are not natively supported.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.github.dyhkwong.sagernet/"/>
<summary>Proxy client</summary>
<published>2025-01-02T18:23:32+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.cabbagelol.bfban/</id>
<title>BFBAN Assistants</title>
<updated>2025-01-02T18:22:06+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Cabbagelol</name>
</author>
<content type="html">应用主要提供 BFBAN.com 在移动设备合适界面，接壤客户端本地图像识别、举报素材管理、预览记录等功能。&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.cabbagelol.bfban/"/>
<summary>联 BAN 的移动应用，在手机上举报玩家</summary>
<published>2025-01-02T18:21:58+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/dev.robin.flip_2_dnd/</id>
<title>Flip 2 DND</title>
<updated>2024-12-29T11:01:55+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Abul Kalam Robin</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Flip 2 DND is a simple yet powerful app that automatically toggles Do Not Disturb mode based on your phone's orientation.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Features:&lt;br>;&lt;br>;- Toggle DND by flipping your phone face down&lt;br>;- Disable DND by flipping your phone face up&lt;br>;- Optional "Only when screen off" mode&lt;br>;- Configurable vibration feedback&lt;br>;- Sound notification when DND is disabled&lt;br>;- Clean, modern Material You design&lt;br>;- No ads, no tracking, completely open source&lt;br>;&lt;br>;The app is designed with privacy and simplicity in mind, requiring only the necessary permissions to function:&lt;br>;&lt;br>;- Access to Do Not Disturb settings&lt;br>;- Vibration control&lt;br>;- Sensor access (accelerometer)&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Perfect for meetings, study sessions, or any time you need quick access to Do Not Disturb mode!&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/dev.robin.flip_2_dnd/"/>
<summary>Toggle Do Not Disturb mode by flipping your phone face down</summary>
<published>2024-12-29T11:01:55+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/de.buttercookie.simbadroid/</id>
<title>SimbaDroid</title>
<updated>2024-12-29T11:00:54+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>buttercookie42</name>
</author>
<content type="html">SimbaDroid ist ein SMB-Server für Android, der es ermöglicht, über WLAN auf die Inhalte deines Telefons zuzugreifen (sowohl den internen Speicher, als auch eine SD-Karte).&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Auf Grund von technischen Beschränkungen von Android benötigt diese App Root-Zugriff (wie auf allen unixoiden Betreibssytemen können Nutzerapps keine Netzwerkports &lt; 1024 öffnen, während der Standardport für SMB wiederum 445 ist und Windows in der Hinsicht auch nicht umkonfiguriert werden kann). Ohne Root-Zugriff benötigst du entweder einen alternativen SMB-Clienten mit einer Einstellmöglichkeit für den Zielport (SimbaDroid benutzt Port 4450 im Hintergrund), oder irgend eine Art von Portmapper-Software um Windows dadurch transparent von Port 445 auf 4450 umzuleiten.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Auf Grund von Einschränkungen von JFileServer wird nur SMBv1 unterstützt, was für moderne Windowssysteme auch nicht ideal ist, aber c'est la vie…&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Da die App hauptsächlich für meinen Eigengebraucht gedacht ist, gibt es momentan keinerlei Konfigurationsmöglichkeiten – Netzwerkfreigaben für den internen Speicher und die externe SD-Karte (falls vorhanden) werden automatisch angelegt, und sind ohne Authentifizierung zugänglich. Sei daher mit der Nutzung dieser App in öffentlichen Netzwerken vorsichtig. Eventuell werde ich in der Zukunft noch Einstellungsmöglichkeiten für die Netzwerkfreigaben und Benutzerauthentifizierung ergänzen, kann dafür aber keinerlei Zeitrahmen versprechen.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;READ/WRITE/MANAGE_EXTERNAL_STORAGE wird für den Zugriff auf das Dateisystem benötigt.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/de.buttercookie.simbadroid/"/>
<summary>A simple SMB file server (needs root)</summary>
<published>2024-12-29T11:00:54+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.hassaneltantawy.alazkar/</id>
<title>Al-Azkar</title>
<updated>2024-12-29T10:58:39+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">- Search Titles&lt;br>;- Add titles to favorites&lt;br>;- Count with app volume keys&lt;br>;- Share zikr as image or as text&lt;br>;- Control app theme&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.hassaneltantawy.alazkar/"/>
<summary>Imam Al-Hafiz Yahya bin Sharafah Al-Din Al-Nawawi.</summary>
<published>2024-12-29T10:58:39+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.gnu.itsmoroto.cifrasoletras/</id>
<title>Cifras o letras</title>
<updated>2024-12-21T16:17:18+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">There are three screens:&lt;br>;* The menu screen, where you can choose language (with it's own statistical letter distribution) and timeout.&lt;br>;* The numbers screen, where you can choose six numbers pushing units or decades and the goal is to get the closest possible to the target number using arithmetic operations.&lt;br>;* The letters screen, where you can choose nine letters pushing vowel or consonant and the goal is to find the largest existing word using these letters.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;The game doesn't resolve any of the puzzles, it's just a random generator of numbers and letters.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.gnu.itsmoroto.cifrasoletras/"/>
<summary>A simplified version of Countdown UK game-show.</summary>
<published>2024-12-21T16:17:18+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/de.swgross.calorimeter/</id>
<title>Calorimeter</title>
<updated>2025-01-02T18:29:31+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Marco Groß (Marco Gross)</name>
</author>
<content type="html">With Calorimeter you can track your daily calorie intake.&lt;br>;Build your own database of your favorite foods.&lt;br>;Or scan the foods that you buy.&lt;br>;As simple as it gets.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/de.swgross.calorimeter/"/>
<summary>Track your calories!</summary>
<published>2024-12-21T16:14:05+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.chenyifaer.fafarunner/</id>
<title>FaFa Runner</title>
<updated>2025-01-02T18:22:30+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>kjxbyz</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Step into the enchanting world of FaFa Runner: Dawn Legends, where an epic adventure awaits! Developed using Flutter and the Flame engine, this RPG delivers a seamless gaming experience with stunning visual effects.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Embark on your journey as a brave adventurer, explore mysterious lands, uncover hidden secrets, and face endless challenges. With rich story-driven quests and diverse character progression systems, every battle offers a unique sense of achievement.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Key Features:&lt;br>;1. Dynamic Combat System: Enjoy intuitive controls and fluid action as you take on powerful enemies and formidable bosses.&lt;br>;2. Gorgeous Visuals: Experience vivid graphics and captivating animations, thanks to the powerful Flutter and Flame engine.&lt;br>;3. Rich Quest System: Engage in main quests and side stories, with each adventure offering surprises and challenges.&lt;br>;4. Customizable Character Growth: Tailor your hero with various skills and equipment to build the ultimate warrior.&lt;br>;5. Interactive World Exploration: Discover hidden treasures and secret locations across a fantastical map.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Join FaFa Runner: Dawn Legends and create your own legendary tale in this magical world. Download now and begin your epic adventure!</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.chenyifaer.fafarunner/"/>
<summary>享受流畅的游戏、令人惊叹的图形和无尽的乐趣</summary>
<published>2024-12-21T16:09:36+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.bartixxx.opflashcontrol/</id>
<title>OnePlus Flash Control</title>
<updated>2024-12-29T10:57:48+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Bartixxx</name>
</author>
<content type="html">OpFlashControl is an advanced LED control application designed specifically for OnePlus devices. With this app, users can control the flashlight and other LED features on their OnePlus phones, including adjusting the brightness and toggling the state of multiple LEDs. The app offers a simple and intuitive interface, allowing users to quickly turn the LED flash on or off, and fine-tune the brightness via a slider.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;To ensure the app works seamlessly, root access is required. This is necessary for the app to interact with system-level files to control the LED settings. This app is ideal for users who want to customize their OnePlus device's LED functionality beyond the stock settings.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Key Features:&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Control LED flash brightness on OnePlus devices.&lt;br>;Toggle between different LED types (white, yellow, or both).&lt;br>;Simple UI with buttons and a brightness slider for easy interaction.&lt;br>;Root access required for full functionality.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.bartixxx.opflashcontrol/"/>
<summary>OnePlus Flash Brightness control app</summary>
<published>2024-12-21T16:08:44+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/at.krixec.ied/</id>
<title>(I)improvised (E)xplosive (D)evices</title>
<updated>2024-12-21T16:06:14+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Krixec</name>
</author>
<content type="html">You thought 8 neighbors was tough?&lt;br>;Well, how about 26?&lt;br>;&lt;br>;This 3D Minesweeper features cubes of various sizes full of deadly explosives to test the limits of your spacial perception.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;If the reception is good I'll add some other shapes you can play around with :)&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/at.krixec.ied/"/>
<summary>Imagine Minesweeper ...
but in 3D</summary>
<published>2024-12-21T16:06:14+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/pw.faraday.faraday/</id>
<title>Faraday</title>
<updated>2025-01-02T18:35:23+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>FaradayApp</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Faraday ist ein Client für das Matrix-Protokoll, der hauptsächlich für die Arbeit mit benutzerdefinierten Servern konfiguriert ist.&lt;br>;Im Vergleich zu anderen Clients ermöglicht es Ihnen, mit der Matrix-Funktionalität flexibler zu arbeiten und mit dem Team zu arbeiten, ohne Datenlecks zu befürchten&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Das Matrix-Protokoll ist eine dezentrale Methode zum Austausch von Nachrichten mit End-to-End-Verschlüsselung, die die gemeinsame Nutzung des Nachrichtenverlaufs auf mehreren Geräten und vieles mehr ermöglicht, das dank unseres Kunden möglich ist&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Faraday hat viele Verbesserungen:&lt;br>;- Unterstützung mehrerer Server in einer Anwendung&lt;br>;- Multi-Account für verschiedene Benutzerserver&lt;br>;- Benachrichtigungen für Multi-Account mit automatischer Übertragung auf den Server, von dem die Benachrichtigung empfangen wurde&lt;br>;- Widgets für die Teamzusammenarbeit mit der Integration von Taiga-Diensten, Cryptpad&lt;br>;- Nuke-Passwort zum Löschen von Anwendungsdaten&lt;br>;- Möglichkeit .onion Verbindung zum Server&lt;br>;- Allgemeine Verbesserungen für den Benutzer&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Faraday hat einen offenen Code: https://github.com/FaradayApp/Faraday-android&lt;br>;Weitere Informationen zum Matrix-Protokoll: https://matrix.org/&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/pw.faraday.faraday/"/>
<summary>Secure messenger for Matrix based on Element</summary>
<published>2024-12-17T17:39:39+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/im.narayana.another/</id>
<title>another.im</title>
<updated>2024-12-17T17:35:39+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">the Another Instant Messenger is not a messenger,&lt;br>;don't believe the words.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;we just offer you a standardized xmpp-client with predicted features which work equally on all platforms.&lt;br>;in our clients we have realized pure XMPP and you won't step on a hedgehog unexpectedly when you communicate with another xmpp client or server.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;because you buy our open-sourced bitcoin,&lt;br>;we decided to offer you to buy our open-sourced messenger.&lt;br>;ha-ha joke.&lt;br>;it's free, really. GPLv3, whatever.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;for Android, it's just an improved fork of Conversations,&lt;br>;&lt;br>;all necessary XEP's was realized by Conversations devs but we added a cherry on top of this.&lt;br>;on the server side we are offering free to use Prosody server,&lt;br>;just connect to [another.im](xmpp:xmppclient-dev@conference.another.im), but we are encouroge you to don't trust us, self-host.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;OTR encryption is also supported as 'secret chats' due to otr has been designed for one-time sessions and the concept of 'secret chats' fully corresponds to the idea of the OTR.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;also you can just download &lt;a href="https://dev.narayana.im/narayana/anotherim">;the source code&lt;/a>;, compile it and install.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;only those who seeks will realize the way to pay us,&lt;br>;we can offer you additional server-side features and some telecommunication magic on our &lt;a href="https://narayana.im">;narayana.im&lt;/a>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/im.narayana.another/"/>
<summary>Yet Another Conversations fork but...</summary>
<published>2024-12-17T17:35:26+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/dev.clombardo.dnsnet/</id>
<title>DNSNet</title>
<updated>2024-12-17T17:35:02+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Charles Lombardo</name>
</author>
<content type="html">DNSNet allows you to take more control over what internet traffic goes in and out of your device. You can download host files to block a set of known advertising or malicious host names and then create exemptions where you see fit.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;It works by creating a lightweight VPN service that filters your internet traffic as you use your device. If you ever have trouble with connecting to a site or using an app, you can always exempt an app from filtering or create an exception for a specific host name.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/dev.clombardo.dnsnet/"/>
<summary>Lightweight ad and content blocker</summary>
<published>2024-12-17T17:35:02+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.schwegelbin.openbible/</id>
<title>OpenBible</title>
<updated>2024-12-29T11:00:02+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>SchweGELBin</name>
</author>
<content type="html">&lt;p>;&lt;i>;OpenBible&lt;/i>; lässt Sie die Bibel in mehreren Übersetzungen herunterladen. Sie können eine heruntergeladene Übersetzung und ein zugehöriges Buch und Kapitel auswählen. Dann können Sie das ausgewählte Kapitel lesen. Wenn Sie die App schließen, speichert es den letzten Stand und Sie können weitermachen, wo Sie aufhörten. Es folgt Ihrem System-Design (Hell-/Dunkelmodus, Sprache und Material Design), um die Erfahrung so leicht und unkompliziert wie möglich zu gestalten.&lt;/p>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.schwegelbin.openbible/"/>
<summary>OpenBible provides the Bible as a simple Android App</summary>
<published>2024-12-17T17:33:31+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.maelchiotti.localmaterialnotes/</id>
<title>Material Notes</title>
<updated>2025-01-02T18:25:31+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Maël Chiotti</name>
</author>
<content type="html">&lt;p>;&lt;b>;Material Notes&lt;/b>; 是基于文本的笔记应用程序，旨在简单。它包含 Material 设计。 它在本地存储笔记，并且没有任何互联网权限，因此您是唯一可以访问笔记的人。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;&lt;b>;做笔记&lt;/b>;&lt;/p>;&lt;ul>;&lt;li>;撰写文本笔记（标题和内容）&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;利用高级格式选项，包括清单&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;编辑时撤销和恢复更改&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;使用主屏幕上的快建操作快速添加笔记&lt;/li>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;p>;&lt;b>;整理&lt;/b>;&lt;/p>;&lt;ul>;&lt;li>;搜索您的笔记&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;按日期或标题、升序或降序对笔记进行排序&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;以列表或网格视图显示笔记&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;置顶您的笔记&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;从回收站中还原已删除的笔记&lt;/li>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;p>;&lt;b>;分享和备份&lt;/b>;&lt;/p>;&lt;ul>;&lt;li>;分享其他应用程序中的文本，将其直接添加到笔记中&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;以文本形式分享笔记&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;手动或自动将笔记导出为 JSON，然后再重新导入&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;将笔记导出为 Markdown&lt;/li>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;p>;&lt;b>;保护&lt;/b>;&lt;/p>;&lt;ul>;&lt;li>;不必担心您的数据如何处理：它无法离开您的设备 因为应用程序没有任何互联网权限&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;加密您的 JSON 导出&lt;/li>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;p>;&lt;b>;定制&lt;/b>;&lt;/p>;&lt;ul>;&lt;li>;选择您的语言&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;选择您的主题（浅色、深色或黑色）&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;选择是否希望主题是动态的（使用背景颜色）&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;选择是要启用高级格式、仅启用清单还是保持基本笔记&lt;/li>;&lt;/ul>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.maelchiotti.localmaterialnotes/"/>
<summary>简单、本地、Material 设计笔记</summary>
<published>2024-12-17T17:33:06+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.example.oj_helper/</id>
<title>oj_helper</title>
<updated>2024-12-17T17:31:59+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Kano07</name>
</author>
<content type="html">一款帮助你查询各大 oj 信息的应用&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.example.oj_helper/"/>
<summary>一款帮助你查询各大 oj 信息的应用</summary>
<published>2024-12-17T17:31:59+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.gnu.itsmoroto.midandpad/</id>
<title>Midandpad</title>
<updated>2024-12-09T10:46:46+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">An Android MIDI controller.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;More information at: https://github.com/pacoandres/midandpad&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;strong>;IMPORTANT: this app is a MIDI controller and doesn't play any sound&lt;/strong>;. For playing sounds it must be connected to a MIDI synthesizer (for example: timidity or fluidsynth)&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.gnu.itsmoroto.midandpad/"/>
<summary>An Android MIDI controller.</summary>
<published>2024-12-09T10:46:46+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.fcitx.fcitx5.android.plugin.thai/</id>
<title>Fcitx5</title>
<updated>2024-12-09T10:46:20+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Fcitx5 for Android Contributors</name>
</author>
<content type="html">No description.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.fcitx.fcitx5.android.plugin.thai/"/>
<summary>Thai input method for Fcitx5</summary>
<published>2024-12-09T10:46:17+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/io.github.poretsky.tuningfork/</id>
<title>Tuning fork</title>
<updated>2024-12-09T10:44:09+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Igor B. Poretsky</name>
</author>
<content type="html">This simple application is intended first of all for those musicians&lt;br>;who like to tune their instruments relying mainly on ears rather than&lt;br>;using various modern tuners with visual indication, or for all who&lt;br>;needs a reference musical tone for any reason. It produces an audible&lt;br>;reference tone by demand just like a classic tuning fork, and, being&lt;br>;installed on a smartphone, is always ready to use.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/io.github.poretsky.tuningfork/"/>
<summary>Reference tones source for musical instruments tuning</summary>
<published>2024-12-09T10:44:09+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/io.github.exclude0122.xivpn/</id>
<title>XiVPN</title>
<updated>2024-12-21T16:15:34+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Exclude0122</name>
</author>
<content type="html">XiVPN is a GUI client for XTLS/Xray-Core, which provides anti-censorship proxy protocols.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Features:&lt;br>;- Fetch proxies from subscription links&lt;br>;- Easy to use GUI&lt;br>;- Configurable proxy settings&lt;br>;- Fully open source&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Supported protocols:&lt;br>;- VLESS&lt;br>;- VMESS&lt;br>;- Shadowsocks&lt;br>;- Trojan&lt;br>;- Wireguard&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Supported transport protocols:&lt;br>;- Websocket&lt;br>;- QUIC&lt;br>;- Httpupgrade&lt;br>;- XHTTP&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Supported security protocols:&lt;br>;- TLS / uTLS&lt;br>;- REALITY</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/io.github.exclude0122.xivpn/"/>
<summary>Proxy client based on XRAY</summary>
<published>2024-12-09T10:44:03+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.logger.app/</id>
<title>Logger</title>
<updated>2025-01-02T18:25:03+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Sanmeet Singh</name>
</author>
<content type="html">&lt;p>;&lt;i>;Logger&lt;/i>; 是一个用户友好的 Android 应用程序，使用 Flutter 构建，可以让您查看和导出通话记录。&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;主要功能：&lt;/b>;&lt;/p>;&lt;ul>;  &lt;li>;&lt;b>;全面的通话记录查看：&lt;/b>; 在应用程序中直接访问和查看您的通话历史。&lt;/li>;  &lt;li>;&lt;b>;便捷的导出选项：&lt;/b>; 以 CSV 或 JSON 格式导出您的通话记录以供分析或存档。&lt;/li>;  &lt;li>;&lt;b>;从生成的 CSV 文件导入通话记录：&lt;/b>; 从应用程序生成的 CSV 文件中导入通话记录，在重置或更换设备后恢复您的通话历史。&lt;/li>;  &lt;li>;&lt;b>;数据安全：&lt;/b>; Logger 优先保护您的隐私，不会将任何通话记录数据存储在我们的服务器上。&lt;/li>;  &lt;li>;&lt;b>;直观的界面：&lt;/b>; 享受简单、用户友好的体验，轻松管理通话记录。&lt;/li>;  &lt;li>;&lt;b>;高级筛选选项：&lt;/b>; 按电话号码、日期范围、通话类型和通话时长筛选通话记录。&lt;/li>;  &lt;li>;&lt;b>;可定制的设备内通话记录分析：&lt;/b>; 在您的设备上直接进行基本统计、通话方向分析和通话时长分析。&lt;/li>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;p>;&lt;b>;优势：&lt;/b>;&lt;/p>;&lt;ul>;  &lt;li>;从以 CSV 或 JSON 格式导出的通话记录中获取洞察。&lt;/li>;  &lt;li>;保持通话记录的组织性，以备将来参考或分析。&lt;/li>;  &lt;li>;在设备上分析通话统计和时长，以便更好地决策。&lt;/li>;  &lt;li>;轻松导出通话记录以实现流畅的数据组织。&lt;/li>;  &lt;li>;在重置或更换设备后，从生成的 CSV 文件中恢复通话历史。&lt;/li>;&lt;/ul>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.logger.app/"/>
<summary>查看并以 CSV 格式导出通话记录</summary>
<published>2024-12-09T10:37:57+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.kjxbyz.picguard/</id>
<title>PicGuard</title>
<updated>2025-01-02T18:24:56+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>kjxbyz</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Introducing PicGuard – the ultimate solution for securing and customizing your digital photos. With our app, you can easily add watermarks to your images to protect your creative work and maintain your privacy.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;PicGuard offers robust privacy protection features, ensuring your personal and sensitive information remains safeguarded. It’s highly customizable, allowing you to personalize watermarks with various fonts, styles, and designs to suit your needs.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Accessible on web, mobile, and desktop, you can seamlessly integrate and manage your watermarking tasks across all your devices. PicGuard, as an open-source tool, it’s not only free but also continuously improved by a community of developers dedicated to providing the best user experience.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Download PicGuard today and take control of your photo security and personalization like never before.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.kjxbyz.picguard/"/>
<summary>给图片添加水印, 防止被恶意使用.</summary>
<published>2024-12-09T10:37:42+00:00</published>
</entry>
</feed>