<feed xml:lang="zh-CN" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<id>https://newapps.f-droid.othing.xyz/new_apps.zh-CN.xml</id>
<title>New apps on F-Droid (zh-CN)</title>
<updated>2024-11-01T08:40:18.593005+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>yzqzss</name>
<email>yzqzss@yandex.com</email>
</author>
<link href="https://newapps.f-droid.othing.xyz/new_apps.zh-CN.xml" rel="self"/>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/" rel="alternate"/>
<generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="1.0.0">python-feedgen</generator>
<subtitle>New apps on F-Droid (zh-CN)</subtitle>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/cn.a10miaomiao.bilidown/</id>
<title>哔哩缓存导出</title>
<updated>2024-10-30T12:39:21+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>10喵喵</name>
</author>
<content type="html">哔哩缓存导出是一个用于导出哔哩哔哩APP离线缓存视频的工具。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;主要功能：&lt;br>;导出哔哩哔哩APP离线缓存视频</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/cn.a10miaomiao.bilidown/"/>
<summary>导出安卓版B站App缓存的视频</summary>
<published>2024-10-30T12:39:11+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.proninyaroslav.blink_comparison/</id>
<title>Blink Comparison</title>
<updated>2024-10-27T19:29:29+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Yaroslav Pronin</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Das Konzept der "Blink Comparison"-Methode ist einfach - die App ermöglicht es, zwischen zwei Fotos eines gleichen Objekt schnell und ohne Verzögerung zu wechseln, um eventuelle Unterschiede einfacherer zu erkennen.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Die Methode der "Blink Comparison" nutzt die hocheffiziente Mustererkennung des menschlichen Auges, um eine schnelle Überprüfung zwischen einem Referenzbild und einem tatsächlich vor Ort aufgenommenen Bild zu ermöglichen. Zum Beispiel zur Erkennung von Manipulationen an kontrastreichen Siegeln aus Nagellack, die zur Sicherung von Manipulationen verwendet werden.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;📋 Merkmale&lt;br>;* Freie und quelloffene Software (FOSS)&lt;br>;* Unterstützung mehrerer Plattformen und Geräte (derzeit nur Android)&lt;br>;* Hinzufügen und Speichern von Referenzbildern in der App oder Aufnahme von Bildern vor Ort; alle Bilder sind verschlüsselt, so dass sie nur schwer gestohlen oder ersetzt werden können&lt;br>;* Vergleichen Sie das Referenzbild mit dem Bild, das Sie gerade aufgenommen haben, indem Sie die Methode der "Blink Comparison" anwenden.&lt;br>;* Hilft dabei, ein Vergleichsfoto in der richtigen Position, mit dem richtigen Winkel, der richtigen Beleuchtung und Entfernung aufzunehmen.&lt;br>;* Material Design&lt;br>;* Nachtmodus&lt;br>;* Responsive UI für verschiedene Geräteformate&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Weitere Informationen finden Sie hier: &lt;a href="https://github.com/proninyaroslav/blink-comparison/blob/HEAD/README.md">;https://github.com/proninyaroslav/blink-comparison/blob/HEAD/README.md&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;Datenschutzerklärung: &lt;a href="https://github.com/proninyaroslav/blink-comparison/blob/HEAD/PRIVACY.md">;https://github.com/proninyaroslav/blink-comparison/blob/HEAD/PRIVACY.md&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.proninyaroslav.blink_comparison/"/>
<summary>Simplifies comparing photos of tamper-evident seals using your eyes</summary>
<published>2024-10-27T19:29:22+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/net.timelegend.chaka.viewer.app/</id>
<title>Chaka Book Reader</title>
<updated>2024-10-27T19:28:33+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">Chaka is an Android app based on MuPDF Android Viewer. It doesn't care about books management. but dedicates to book reading experience, with most expected features:&lt;br>;Horizontal / Vertical Flipping.&lt;br>;Right-to-Left Forward reading mode, for some reverse reading direction books.&lt;br>;Single Column mode, to work with Scanned Dual-Spread PDF documents.&lt;br>;Cropping Margin, to get more visible reading area.&lt;br>;Focus mode.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/net.timelegend.chaka.viewer.app/"/>
<summary>An excellent Android book reader based on MuPDF Android Viewer</summary>
<published>2024-10-27T19:28:33+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.fossify.camera/</id>
<title>Fossify Camera</title>
<updated>2024-10-25T00:36:13+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Fossify</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Fossify Camera is your go-to app for capturing life’s moments with precision and privacy. Whether you’re snapping photos or recording videos, this fully customizable, privacy-respecting camera app is designed to meet your needs.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;📸 YOUR PRIVACY, OUR PRIORITY:&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;With the Fossify Camera app, your data remains private. Enjoy a camera that works without internet access or intrusive permissions, ensuring your photos and videos stay secure.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;🚀 SEAMLESS PERFORMANCE:&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Fossify Camera provides a fluid and responsive interface. Switch between photo and video modes, adjust zoom, and toggle between front and rear cameras instantly. Capture moments with zero lag and experience smooth performance at all times.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;🖼️ COMPLETE CUSTOMIZATION:&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Personalize every aspect of your camera experience. Adjust the output quality, customize the save path, and set the resolution to suit your needs. You can even customize colors and themes to match your style.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;⚡ DYNAMIC CONTROLS:&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Toggle settings with ease—control flash, aspect ratio, and zoom directly from the camera view. The app is designed for quick access, letting you capture moments efficiently, with intuitive controls.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;🖼️ MATERIAL DESIGN:&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Enjoy a sleek, user-friendly interface with material design and a dynamic theme that adapts to your preferences. Whether you're using the app during the day or at night, Fossify Camera provides a smooth and intuitive experience.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;🌐 OPEN-SOURCE ASSURANCE:&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Fossify Camera is built on an open-source foundation. With our commitment to transparency, you can review the code on GitHub and be part of a community that values privacy and trust.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Fossify Camera offers everything you need to capture moments effortlessly while respecting your privacy.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Explore more Fossify apps: https://www.fossify.org&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Open-Source Code: https://www.github.com/FossifyOrg&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Join the community on Reddit: https://www.reddit.com/r/Fossify&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Connect on Telegram: https://t.me/Fossify&lt;br>;&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.fossify.camera/"/>
<summary>Lightweight open-source camera app for quick, easy, and secure photography</summary>
<published>2024-10-25T00:36:13+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.fossify.calculator/</id>
<title>Fossify 计算器</title>
<updated>2024-10-25T00:36:09+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Fossify</name>
</author>
<content type="html">隆重推出 Fossify 计算器——您的多功能高效工具，可满足您的所有计算需求。享受时尚、现代的设计和强大的功能，非常适合简单的计算和货币兑换等更复杂的任务。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;📶 离线功能：&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Fossify 计算器完全离线运行，无需互联网权限。随时随地使用，体验增强的隐私、安全性和稳定性。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;🌐 多种功能：&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;无论您是需要乘法、除法、计算根和幂，还是转换货币，Fossify 计算器都能满足您的需求。它非常适合日常计算和抵押贷款计算更专业的任务。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;📳 可自定义设置：&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;通过自定义设置定制您的体验。切换按钮按下时的振动，防止您的手机在使用应用时息屏，并根据您的喜好调整界面。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;🔒 隐私和安全：&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;您的隐私至关重要。Fossify 计算器不会收集或与第三方共享任何用户信息。放心使用本应用，因为您知道您的数据是安全的。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;📊 操作历史：&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;访问您的计算历史以供快速参考。轻松浏览最近的操作以查看或继续您的工作。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;🎨 个性化体验：&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;使用可自定义的颜色对计算器进行个性化设置。调整文本和背景颜色以符合您的风格和偏好，创建视觉上吸引人且易于使用的界面。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;🌐 开源透明度：&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Fossify 计算器完全开源，提供透明度和安全性。访问源代码进行审计，确保工具值得信赖和可靠。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;使用 Fossify 计算器体验更高水平的效率和自定义。立即下载，提升您的计算体验。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;探索更多 Fossify 应用：https://www.fossify.org&lt;br>;&lt;br>;开源代码：https://www.github.com/FossifyOrg&lt;br>;&lt;br>;加入 Reddit 社区：https://www.reddit.com/r/Fossify&lt;br>;&lt;br>;在 Telegram 上联系：https://t.me/Fossify&lt;br>;&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.fossify.calculator/"/>
<summary>简单、开源的计算器，可快速、轻松地计算</summary>
<published>2024-10-25T00:36:09+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/net.diffengine.romandigitalclock/</id>
<title>RomanDigital</title>
<updated>2024-10-25T00:34:41+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>David Yockey</name>
</author>
<content type="html">The RomanDigital app provides a clock of unique style that can be used to repurpose an old device or to display time on a current model.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;For more personal use, the RomanDigital widget makes a distinctive addition to a device's Home screen.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;RomanDigital includes features expected in an ordinary digital clock app, such as:&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Choice of 12 or 24 hour format&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Optional AM/PM indicator (uniquely integrated into the time display)&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Option to keep display on when app is in the foreground&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Display in either portrait or landscape&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;For more detailed information including a FAQ list, please see the README.md file accompanying the RomanDigital source code.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Source code for RomanDigital is available at:&lt;br>;https://github.com/dfyockey/RomanDigital</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/net.diffengine.romandigitalclock/"/>
<summary>Digital Clock App and Widget with Roman Numeral Display</summary>
<published>2024-10-25T00:34:41+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/micro.repl.ma7moud3ly/</id>
<title>Micro REPL</title>
<updated>2024-10-25T00:34:27+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>ma7moud3ly</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Micro REPL has the following features:&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;A &lt;strong>;Terminal&lt;/strong>; to access MicroPython interactive interpreter.&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Files &lt;strong>;Explorer&lt;/strong>; (Files Manager) for MicroPython storage.&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;A Smart &lt;strong>;Code Editor&lt;/strong>; with python syntax support and code completion.&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/micro.repl.ma7moud3ly/"/>
<summary>MicroPython IDE</summary>
<published>2024-10-25T00:34:27+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.paddlesandbugs.dahdidahdit/</id>
<title>Dahdidahdit</title>
<updated>2024-10-25T00:31:48+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">&lt;p>;&lt;br>;Ham radio ops who like QRP will sooner or later want to learn Morse code so they &lt;br>;can communicate using CW. This app teaches not only amateur radio enthusiasts &lt;br>;how Morse code works and trains practitioners so they get faster.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;p>;&lt;br>;You set your current level of proficiency and what you aim for (e.g. all letters &lt;br>;with 20 words per minute). Dahdidahdit guides you from where you are to where &lt;br>;to want to be: it teaches you new letters when you are ready and increases your &lt;br>;speed when you seem bored. The only things you need other than a phone and the &lt;br>;app is a sheet of paper and a pen. When you start the session, Dahdidahdit&lt;br>;plays Morse code letters you know at the speed you are comfortable with. You jot &lt;br>;down the letters you recognized. When the session ends, Dahdidahdit shows you &lt;br>;what it sent and you compare notes. Then you tap the button that shows the &lt;br>;proper number of mistakes. When you complete enough practice sessions with only &lt;br>;few mistakes, Dahdidahdit starts the next lesson - be it by introducing a new &lt;br>;letter or by increasing the speed.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;p>;&lt;br>;Other features include learning Q-code and sending practice using either an &lt;br>;on-screen or an actual paddle, connected by USB.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.paddlesandbugs.dahdidahdit/"/>
<summary>An actual Morse code trainer, not just a Morse code generator</summary>
<published>2024-10-25T00:31:48+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.fossify.home/</id>
<title>Fossify Launcher</title>
<updated>2024-10-20T09:03:23+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Fossify</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Fossify Launcher is your gateway to a fast, personalized, and privacy-first home screen experience. No ads, no bloat – just a smooth, efficient launcher designed to fit your unique style and preferences.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;🚀 LIGHTNING-FAST NAVIGATION:&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Navigate your device with speed and precision. Fossify Launcher is optimized to be responsive and fluid, giving you instant access to your favorite apps without lag.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;🎨 FULL CUSTOMIZATION:&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Tailor your home screen with dynamic themes, custom colors, and layouts. Personalize your launcher to match your style with easy-to-use tools that let you create a truly unique setup.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;🖼️ COMPLETE WIDGET SUPPORT:&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Integrate fully resizable widgets with ease. Whether you need clocks, calendars, or other handy tools, Fossify Launcher ensures they blend seamlessly into your home screen design.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;📱 NO UNWANTED CLUTTER:&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Effortlessly manage your apps by hiding or uninstalling them in just a few taps, keeping your home screen organized and clutter-free.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;🔒 PRIVACY AND SECURITY:&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Your privacy is at the heart of Fossify Launcher. With no internet access and no intrusive permissions, your data stays with you. No tracking, no ads – just a launcher built to respect your privacy.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;🌐 OPEN-SOURCE ASSURANCE:&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Fossify Launcher is built on an open-source foundation, allowing you to review our code on GitHub, fostering trust and a community committed to privacy.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Find your balance of speed, customization, and privacy with Fossify Launcher.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Explore more Fossify apps: https://www.fossify.org&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Open-Source Code: https://www.github.com/FossifyOrg&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Join the community on Reddit: https://www.reddit.com/r/Fossify&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Connect on Telegram: https://t.me/Fossify&lt;br>;&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.fossify.home/"/>
<summary>Customize your home screen with a fast, ad-free, open-source launcher</summary>
<published>2024-10-20T09:03:23+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/de.bahnhoefe.deutschlands.bahnhofsfotos/</id>
<title>Railway station photos</title>
<updated>2024-10-20T08:53:09+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Railwaystations Team</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Mit der Bahnhofsfotos-App kannst Du das OpenData Projekt https://railway-Stations.org unterstützen. Wähle ein Land und finde Bahnhöfe zu denen wir noch kein Bahnhofsfoto auf http://www.deutschlands-bahnhoefe.de / https://railway-stations.org haben. Inzwischen sind über 20 Länder in unserer Datenbank. Weitere werden Stück für Stück hinzugefügt.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Im Menüpunkt "Deine Daten" gibst Du an, wie Du die Fotos schicken möchtest - als verlinkter Fotograf oder anonym, mit Lizenz ohne Namensnennung und ob Du das Foto selbst geknipst hast. Wenn Du verlinkt werden möchtest, benötigen wir den Link und den Nicknamen zu z.B. Deinem Twitter-Account.&lt;br>;Wenn Du einen Token anforderst, kannst Du Deine Fotos auch hochladen.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Mittles Klick auf das Suchsymbol oben im Startbildschirm, kannst Du eine Volltextsuche auslösen.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Im Menüpunkt "Bahnhofskarte" kannst Du Deinen Standord ermitteln und Bahnhöfe in der Nähe finden. Es lässt sich filtern, ob Du nur Bahnhöfe mit oder ohne Foto sehen möchtest. &lt;br>;&lt;br>;Melde inaktive oder fehlende Bahnhöfe über die App.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Du kannst auch auswählen, ob Du benachrichtigt werden möchtest, wenn sich ein Bahnhof in unmittelbarer Nähe befindet. </content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/de.bahnhoefe.deutschlands.bahnhofsfotos/"/>
<summary>Collect photos of railway stations for https://railway-stations.org</summary>
<published>2024-10-20T08:53:09+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.woheller69.PeakOrama/</id>
<title>PeakOrama</title>
<updated>2024-10-27T19:29:50+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>woheller69</name>
</author>
<content type="html">PeakOrama zeigt die Berggipfel rund um einen Standort mithilfe der PeakFinder-API.&lt;br>;Der Standort kann entweder über die Photon-API oder über das GPS Ihres Geräts gesucht werden.&lt;br>;Die Ansicht kann manuell auf dem Bildschirm gedreht werden oder basierend auf dem eingebauten Kompass Ihres Geräts oder über die Bewegungsrichtung.&lt;br>;Falls Ihr Kompass auch nach der Kalibrierung eine Abweichung aufweist, besteht die Möglichkeit, die Abweichung zu korrigieren.&lt;br>;Das Setzen von Markierungen wird nicht unterstützt.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Für die Nutzung dieser App ist eine funktionierende Internetverbindung erforderlich.&lt;br>;Für jeden Standort werden etwa 5-10 MB Daten heruntergeladen. Achten Sie also auf Ihren Datenverbrauch.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.woheller69.PeakOrama/"/>
<summary>PeakOrama shows mountains around a location</summary>
<published>2024-10-17T09:01:46+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.electrum.electrum/</id>
<title>Electrum Bitcoin Wallet</title>
<updated>2024-10-27T19:29:08+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>spesmilo</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Electrum Bitcoin wallet for Android.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Secure, feature rich and trusted by the Bitcoin community since 2011.&lt;br>;• Website: https://electrum.org&lt;br>;• Email: electrumdev@gmail.com&lt;br>;• GitHub: https://github.com/spesmilo/electrum&lt;br>;• Support: Please use GitHub or email to report bugs rather than the app rating system.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Features:&lt;br>;• Safe: Your private keys are encrypted and never leave your device.&lt;br>;• Forgiving: Your wallet can be recovered from a secret phrase.&lt;br>;• Instant On: Electrum uses servers that index the Bitcoin blockchain making it fast.&lt;br>;• No Lock-In: You can export your private keys and use them in other Bitcoin clients.&lt;br>;• No Downtimes: Electrum servers are decentralized and redundant. Your wallet is never down.&lt;br>;• Proof Checking: Electrum Wallet verifies all the transactions in your history using SPV.&lt;br>;• Cold Storage: Keep your private keys offline and go online with a watching-only wallet.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.electrum.electrum/"/>
<summary>Fast and self-custodial wallet for Bitcoin and the Lightning Network</summary>
<published>2024-10-17T08:56:23+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/io.github.project_kaat.gpsdrelay/</id>
<title>gpsdRelay</title>
<updated>2024-10-17T08:51:20+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>project-kaat</name>
</author>
<content type="html">This app allows you to utilize an Android device's GPS chip as a gpsd location data provider. UDP or TCP transport protocols are supported for supplying NMEA messages to the daemon.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/io.github.project_kaat.gpsdrelay/"/>
<summary>Relay NMEA information from Android to gpsd.</summary>
<published>2024-10-17T08:51:20+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/github.paroj.dsub2000/</id>
<title>DSub2000</title>
<updated>2024-10-17T08:49:25+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Pavel Rojtberg</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Connect to your Subsonic server and listen to your music wherever you go. Songs&lt;br>;are cached for playback to save on your mobile bandwidth and to make them&lt;br>;available when you have no connection at all.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Subsonic is a cross-platform FOSS media server that's capable of indexing very&lt;br>;large media collections. The server can transcode if necessary so that the app&lt;br>;can play files that your device may not normally support.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;h2>;Features&lt;/h2>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Drag and drop songs to rearrange your playlist on the Now Playing tab&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Pause playback when other apps request audio focus (navigation, etc)&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Lockscreen controls&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Gapless Playback&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Highly customizable UI&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;User defined Cache Size, Network Timeout, and Buffer Length&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/github.paroj.dsub2000/"/>
<summary>Android client for Subsonic servers.</summary>
<published>2024-10-17T08:49:25+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/de.tutao.calendar/</id>
<title>Tuta Calendar</title>
<updated>2024-10-17T08:47:27+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Tutao GmbH</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Take your privacy to the next level with the secure Tuta Calendar app. This encrypted time-management tool is the most private way to organize your busy schedule – and it’s quick to navigate, comes with dark and light mode, plus, it’s perfectly integrated with the Tuta Mail app.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;SECURE CALENDAR&lt;br>;&lt;br>;* Quantum-safe encryption: End-to-end encrypted data exchange with all Tuta Calendar users and with users of other calendar apps (via optional password-protected event invites).&lt;br>;* No ads, no tracking, and no data sharing: We protect your privacy.&lt;br>;* Zero-knowledge architecture: Entire events, including event notifications, are encrypted and hidden from our servers. We do not know when your meetings are taking place, who they are with, or what they are about.&lt;br>;* Based in Germany: All data is safeguarded by strict German data protection laws.&lt;br>;* Fully GDPR-compliant&lt;br>;&lt;br>;FULLY FEATURED&lt;br>;&lt;br>;* **SYNC ON ALL DEVICES:** Your Tuta planner syncs automatically on all devices and browsers.&lt;br>;* **RECURRING EVENTS:** Use daily, weekly, monthly, yearly or custom repetitions.&lt;br>;* **MULTIPLE CALENDAR VIEWS:** Switch in one tap between agenda, daily, weekly, and monthly view.&lt;br>;* **SYNC EXTERNAL CALENDARS:** Events will automatically sync if the owner adds or updates events or meetings on external calendars. Once subscribed, no action is needed.&lt;br>;* **MANAGE UNLIMITED CALENDARS (paid feature):** You can toggle different calendars into view with a single press or leave all events visible for a complete overview.&lt;br>;* **EVENT REMINDERS:** Never miss a date. Tuta’s zero-knowledge reminders make sure you never miss an appointment.&lt;br>;* **LINK CALENDAR EVENTS TO EMAILS AND CONTACTS:** Your Tuta Calendar is directly linked to your Tuta Mail account, so when creating events you can easily invite your contacts or send invites to others via email.&lt;br>;* **OFFLINE SUPPORT:** Independent standalone app so you can check your schedule both online and offline!</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/de.tutao.calendar/"/>
<summary>Quantum-safe encrypted planner to schedule &amp; manage your events &amp; sync calendars</summary>
<published>2024-10-17T08:47:27+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.willie.mancala/</id>
<title>Mancala</title>
<updated>2024-10-17T08:44:48+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Willie</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Mancala is a traditional board game that involves strategy, counting, and some luck. This implementation of Mancala is developed for Android, allowing players to enjoy the game on their mobile devices. For the command-line interface (CLI) implementation, see https://github.com/Willie169/mancala-cli.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.willie.mancala/"/>
<summary>Mancala Game</summary>
<published>2024-10-17T08:44:48+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.wbpxre150.unjumbleapp/</id>
<title>unjumble</title>
<updated>2024-10-17T08:44:45+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Adam Bullock</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Unjumble all 4364 words using the pictures as a hint.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.wbpxre150.unjumbleapp/"/>
<summary>an anagram game with picture hints</summary>
<published>2024-10-17T08:44:45+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.inky.fitnesscalendar/</id>
<title>Fitness Calendar</title>
<updated>2024-10-17T08:38:20+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Inky</name>
</author>
<content type="html">## Features&lt;br>;&lt;br>;- Track activities of all kinds&lt;br>;- Activity recording&lt;br>;- Gpx import&lt;br>;- Create custom activity types&lt;br>;- Statistics&lt;br>;- Basic diary functionality</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.inky.fitnesscalendar/"/>
<summary>A private and fully offline activity tracker.</summary>
<published>2024-10-17T08:38:20+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.github.umer0586.sensagram/</id>
<title>Sensa Gram</title>
<updated>2024-10-27T19:22:26+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Umer Farooq</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Transform your Android device into a dynamic sensor hub with Sensagram, offering seamless real-time data streaming. Sensagram allows you to seamlessly stream live sensor data over UDP, ensuring low latency&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Effortlessly broadcast a wide range of Android sensors, including motion, position, environmental, and GPS (location) data, directly to a specified IP address or server, making it the perfect tool for developers, researchers, and tech enthusiasts.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Key Features:&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Real-time Streaming: Transmit sensor data in real time for accurate and immediate feedback.&lt;br>;Comprehensive Sensor Support: Stream data from motion (gyroscope, accelerometer), position (magnetic field, rotation vector), environmental (light, temperature), and GPS (location) sensors.&lt;br>;Low Latency with UDP: Experience the speed and efficiency of UDP, providing minimal delay in data transmission, ideal for time-sensitive applications.&lt;br>;Customizable Endpoints: Easily configure and send data to your desired IP address or network endpoint.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;In the app, select the desired sensors from the list and tap the "Stream" button. This will begin transmitting sensor data to the specified address. To receive the data, you'll need to set up a UDP server. The app sends the data in JSON format.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;For complete guidance please visit https://github.com/umer0586/SensaGram&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.github.umer0586.sensagram/"/>
<summary>Stream Android sensor data over UDP with minimal latency.</summary>
<published>2024-10-17T08:37:30+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.bibleside.bibleside/</id>
<title>Bibleside</title>
<updated>2024-10-17T08:33:55+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Noah Rahm</name>
</author>
<content type="html">A simple, offline Bible app featuring the Open English Translation: a new, open-licensed Bible translation.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;The OET (Open English Translation) is a new, open-licensed Bible translation (currently in draft state) featuring multiple versions intended to be used together. Please see the OET website (https://openenglishtranslation.bible) for more information on what makes it different than other translations.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;FEATURES&lt;br>;- Contains the OET Reader's version, OET literal version, and the KJV version.&lt;br>;- Read Bible versions together with linked scrolling.&lt;br>;- Adjust text size and switch between light, dark, sepia, and high contrast themes.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Bibleside is currently in alpha, with more features and improvements planned. Feedback is welcome!</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.bibleside.bibleside/"/>
<summary>Offline Bible app featuring the OET (Open English Translation)</summary>
<published>2024-10-17T08:33:55+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.exbin.bined.editor.android/</id>
<title>BinEd - Binary/Hex Editor</title>
<updated>2024-10-20T09:03:05+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">BinEd is a hex editor tool, which allows to directly browse and edit content of any file or binary data.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;App is currently beta with limited functionality.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Features&lt;br>;--------&lt;br>;&lt;br>;- Visualize data as numerical (hexadecimal) codes and text representation&lt;br>;- Codes can be also binary, octal or decimal&lt;br>;- Support for Unicode, UTF-8 and other charsets&lt;br>;- Insert and overwrite edit modes&lt;br>;- TODO: Searching for text / hexadecimal code with matching highlighting&lt;br>;- Support for undo/redo&lt;br>;- TODO: Support for files with size up to exabytes&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Translations&lt;br>;------------&lt;br>;&lt;br>;- Hindi: Govind S Nair&lt;br>;&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.exbin.bined.editor.android/"/>
<summary>Editor for binary data (hex viewer/editor)</summary>
<published>2024-10-13T10:12:48+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.tharunbirla.fetchit/</id>
<title>FetchIt</title>
<updated>2024-10-27T19:24:13+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">Welcome to FetchIt! Easily download media from your favorite platforms and save it to your device. 🎥📸&lt;br>;&lt;br>;**Supported Platforms:**&lt;br>;&lt;br>;* YouTube&lt;br>;* Facebook&lt;br>;* Instagram&lt;br>;* Twitter&lt;br>;* TikTok&lt;br>;* Reddit&lt;br>;* Vimeo&lt;br>;* Dailymotion&lt;br>;* Pinterest&lt;br>;* Snapchat&lt;br>;* SoundCloud&lt;br>;* Twitch&lt;br>;* Tumblr&lt;br>;* Bilibili&lt;br>;* Loom&lt;br>;* Streamable&lt;br>;* VK&lt;br>;* Rutube&lt;br>;* Bluesky&lt;br>;* Vine&lt;br>;* OK&lt;br>;&lt;br>;⚠️ **Disclaimer**: The app developer does not have any relationship or agreement with any of the platforms listed above.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;For more info or to report issues, visit the [GitHub repository](https://github.com/tharunbirla/FetchIt/issues).&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.tharunbirla.fetchit/"/>
<summary>FetchIt download video from YouTube, Twitter, Instagram, Facebook, and more.</summary>
<published>2024-10-13T09:58:55+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.nemesis.droidcrypt/</id>
<title>DroidCrypt</title>
<updated>2024-10-27T19:23:41+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">Description:&lt;br>;&lt;br>;File and text encryption in Android offers crucial benefits in protecting sensitive data. By encrypting files and text, users can prevent unauthorized access, ensuring confidentiality and privacy. This is especially vital in a world where mobile devices often contain personal, financial, and business-related information. Encryption adds an additional layer of security, preventing malicious actors from intercepting or tampering with data, thus mitigating the risk of data breaches and identity theft.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Features:&lt;br>;&lt;br>;  -  Uses AES-256-GCM for encryption&lt;br>;&lt;br>;  -  Uses Scrypt for key derivation with CPU/Memory cost of 32768, block size of 16, and parallelization of 4&lt;br>;&lt;br>;  -  Built in Java&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.nemesis.droidcrypt/"/>
<summary>A file and text encryption tool for Android</summary>
<published>2024-10-13T09:56:04+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.justdeax.composeStopwatch/</id>
<title>Compose Stopwatch</title>
<updated>2024-10-25T00:30:32+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">Android-Stoppuhr-App im Material You-Design, entwickelt für einfache Bedienung und beste Funktionen&lt;br>;&lt;br>;► Kreisförtiger Fortschritt&lt;br>;    • Zeigt den Fortschritt der aktuellen Runde basierend auf der allerersten an&lt;br>;    • Ein Strich auf dem Rundenfortschritt zeigt die vorherige Runde an&lt;br>;&lt;br>;► Thema ändern, neue Themen verfügbar&lt;br>;    • Dynamisches Thema ist nur ab Android 12+ verfügbar&lt;br>;    • Extra Dunkel-Thema spart Akku bei AMOLED-Bildschirmen&lt;br>;&lt;br>;► Ausrichtung ändern&lt;br>;    • Porträtmodus bietet mehr Platz für Runden&lt;br>;    • Im Querformat ist der Zeittext größer&lt;br>;&lt;br>;► Wählen Sie eine Aktion aus, wenn Sie auf die Zeit anzeigende Uhr tippen&lt;br>;    • Fortsetzen oder Pause&lt;br>;    • Fortsetzen oder Runde hinzufügen&lt;br>;    • Fortsetzen oder Stopp&lt;br>;    • Wenn Sie dies nicht möchten, können Sie die Aktion entfernen&lt;br>;&lt;br>;► Benachrichtigungen ein-/ausschalten&lt;br>;    • Stoppuhr-Steuerung in Benachrichtigungen&lt;br>;    • Bei Deaktivierung arbeitet die Stoppuhr mit ViewModel und DataStore&lt;br>;    • Bei Aktivierung arbeitet die Stoppuhr mit LifecycleService und ForegroundService&lt;br>;&lt;br>;► Bildschirm-Wachmodus&lt;br>;    • Möglichkeit, die Stoppuhr zu beobachten, ohne dass der Bildschirm in den Ruhezustand geht</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.justdeax.composeStopwatch/"/>
<summary>Stopwatch in the Material You theme, designed for ease of use and best features</summary>
<published>2024-10-13T09:54:00+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/chat.seers.app/</id>
<title>Seers Lodge</title>
<updated>2024-10-27T19:21:17+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>NAND</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Seers Lodge is a feature-rich chat application that runs on the Tox protocol.&lt;br>;This app is designed to be a modern, decentralized alternative to mainstream chat apps without sacrificing the features "we all know and love".&lt;br>;&lt;br>;"Features? What kind?"&lt;br>;- Decentralized P2P calling and messaging&lt;br>;- Peer-to-peer file sharing 👮🏿&lt;br>;- Role-based group chat&lt;br>;- Custom avatars&lt;br>;- Message reactions 👍&lt;br>;- Text effects and styles&lt;br>;- Animated emojis and GIFs&lt;br>;- Embedded URL previews&lt;br>;- Voicemail!&lt;br>;&lt;br>;And much more to come!</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/chat.seers.app/"/>
<summary>P2P Chat Application</summary>
<published>2024-10-13T09:48:14+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.github.msx80.retrodrawing/</id>
<title>RetroDrawing</title>
<updated>2024-10-07T06:38:28+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>msx80</name>
</author>
<content type="html">A drawing app with low resolution and a fixed 32 color palette. Has various tool: small, medium and large pen, fill bucket, color picker, full undo support etc.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.github.msx80.retrodrawing/"/>
<summary>A simple drawing app with big pixels and fixed palette.</summary>
<published>2024-10-07T06:38:28+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/alt.nainapps.aer/</id>
<title>Aer - Fork of Anemo</title>
<updated>2024-10-17T08:30:41+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">Aer is a private local (+secondary) storage utility application for android.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Do you worry about your private pictures or files appearing in other apps?&lt;br>;That's where Aer private storage comes in. Files in Aer storage won't appear in the other apps.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Instead of being a stand-alone file manager user interface, it hooks into various components of&lt;br>;Android making it feel like a native part of the operative system.&lt;br>;Moreover it provides ways for the user to export contents from other apps and save them as files.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Features&lt;br>;&lt;br>;- Create folders and organize files freely&lt;br>;- All files in the private storage won't appear in the other apps&lt;br>;- Access in the system Files application (the _DocumentsProviderUI_)&lt;br>;    - An optional shortcut for devices that do not expose the system Files app is offered&lt;br>;- Lock access to the private storage&lt;br>;  - Quick tile&lt;br>;  - Auto lock after 15 minutes&lt;br>;  - Password for locking access to the files&lt;br>;- Import content using the share Android functionality&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Aer vs Anemo&lt;br>;&lt;br>;In addition to Anemo features above, Aer adds support for external storage, like encrypted SD cards.&lt;br>;When available Aer will store your files on external storage (which tend to have larger capacity).&lt;br>;This also allows accessing your private files on your computer when connected using USB (MTP).&lt;br>;The storage backend used is also manually configurable.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/alt.nainapps.aer/"/>
<summary>Private storage utility for android with support for external storage media</summary>
<published>2024-10-07T06:29:30+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/futuristicgoo.emotic/</id>
<title>Emotic</title>
<updated>2024-10-13T10:05:23+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>FuturisticGoo</name>
</author>
<content type="html">&lt;b>;A simple app which lists a bunch of emoticons (not emojis!).&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Features:&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Browse through a list of emoticons which you can copy to clipboard&lt;br>;without using internet or any websites.&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Add or modify your own emoticons.&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Search using related tags.&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;App is written in Flutter, using Material 3 and supports dark/light mode.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/futuristicgoo.emotic/"/>
<summary>Reignite the love for emoticons</summary>
<published>2024-10-03T07:07:01+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.jherkenhoff.qalculate/</id>
<title>Qalculate!</title>
<updated>2024-10-03T06:58:49+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Jost Herkenhoff</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Qalculate! - the ultimate multi-purpose calculator - is now finally available on Android!&lt;br>;&lt;br>;It is simple to use but provides power and versatility normally reserved for complicated math packages, as well as useful tools for everyday needs (such as currency conversion and percent calculation). Features include a large library of customizable functions, unit calculations and conversion, physical constants, symbolic calculations (including integrals and equations), arbitrary precision, uncertainty propagation or interval arithmetic.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.jherkenhoff.qalculate/"/>
<summary>Powerful and versatile multi-purpose calculator</summary>
<published>2024-10-03T06:58:44+00:00</published>
</entry>
</feed>