<feed xml:lang="zh-CN" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<id>https://newapps.f-droid.othing.xyz/new_apps.zh-CN.xml</id>
<title>New apps on F-Droid (zh-CN)</title>
<updated>2024-02-23T08:43:09.938268+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>yzqzss</name>
<email>yzqzss@yandex.com</email>
</author>
<link href="https://newapps.f-droid.othing.xyz/new_apps.zh-CN.xml" rel="self"/>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/" rel="alternate"/>
<generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="1.0.0">python-feedgen</generator>
<subtitle>New apps on F-Droid (zh-CN)</subtitle>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/soko.ekibun.stitch/</id>
<title>Stitch</title>
<updated>2024-02-19T13:59:12+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>ekibun</name>
</author>
<content type="html">1. 点击导入/截图添加图片&lt;br>;2. 截图模式下，点击悬浮按钮添加屏幕截图，长按按钮打开编辑窗口&lt;br>;3. 点击圆圈选择图片修改拼接参数，或拖动圆圈移动位置&lt;br>;4. 自动拼接采用 opencv 计算，可以用于拼接地图，请保持足够的重合区域&lt;br>;5. 拼接数据将在软件重启或点击快捷按钮后清除，编辑完成后请尽快导出&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/soko.ekibun.stitch/"/>
<summary>拼接屏幕截图</summary>
<published>2024-02-19T13:59:12+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.theripper.cb_app/</id>
<title>Cb_app: Client for using CommonBooking websites </title>
<updated>2024-02-17T07:59:08+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">&lt;b>;cb_app&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;Cb_app is a Flutter based App that provides Access to &lt;a href="https://github.com/wielebenwir/commonsbooking">;CommonsBooking&lt;/a>; driven Sites.  It provides an alternative User Interface as a local running App for different Operating Systems.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;Prerequisits&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;For read access, the site must have the CommonsAPI enabled&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;For write access (login and booking), the companion Plugin (cb-appapi) has to be installed&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;Functions&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;em>;With CommonsAPI enabled:&lt;/em>;&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;View available Stations in a Map and List View&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Show Location information&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Show Item Information&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;View availability of items in Calendar View&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Caching of information for offline view&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;em>;With companion Plugin (cb-appapi):&lt;/em>;&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Login as User&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Make Bookings&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;List current and future privae bookings&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Manage current and future private bookings&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.theripper.cb_app/"/>
<summary>View sites that are driven by CommonsBooking and manage your bookings</summary>
<published>2024-02-17T07:59:08+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.fossify.musicplayer/</id>
<title>Fossify Music Player</title>
<updated>2024-02-15T12:24:52+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Fossify</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Introducing Fossify Music Player – your gateway to uninterrupted musical enjoyment. Say goodbye to intrusive ads and hello to a seamless music experience designed to accompany you wherever you go.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🚫 AD-FREE LISTENING:&lt;br>;We understand the value of your time and the sanctity of your music experience. That's why Fossify Music Player is completely ad-free. No distractions, just pure musical bliss. Whether you're at home, on the go, or exploring the great outdoors, enjoy your music without interruptions.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;📶 OFFLINE ACCESS:&lt;br>;Take your music with you wherever you go, even to mars. Fossify Music Player operates offline, ensuring you can enjoy your favorite tracks anytime, anywhere, without needing an internet connection.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🚀 LIGHTNING-FAST AND EFFICIENT:&lt;br>;Worried about draining your battery while indulging in your favorite tunes? Despite its rich features, Fossify Music Player maintains a small app size, ensuring quick and hassle-free download and installation. Experience swift navigation and seamless performance while indulging in your favorite melodies.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🎚️ POWERFUL EQUALIZER:&lt;br>;Elevate your listening experience with our powerful equalizer, offering a range of presets to suit every genre and audio preference. Adjust the music effects based on your mood, genre, or even your audio setup for an immersive sound experience.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🌙 SLEEP TIMER FOR RELAXING NIGHTS:&lt;br>;Soothe your nights with the Sleep Timer feature. Choose your favorite tunes and let them gently fade away as you drift off to sleep. Enjoy a peaceful night's rest without worrying about the music playing on.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;📜 PLAYLIST MANAGEMENT:&lt;br>;Create and manage your playlists effortlessly. Organize your music library, customize track labels, and even edit song information to your liking. Shuffle, repeat, skip, and forward your tracks with ease.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🔒 PRIVACY ASSURED:&lt;br>;Your privacy is our top priority. Fossify Music Player does not collect or share any user information with third parties. Enjoy peace of mind knowing that your musical journey remains private and secure.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🌈 MODERN DESIGN &amp; USER-FRIENDLY INTERFACE:&lt;br>;Enjoy a clean, modern design with a user-friendly interface. The app features a material design and a dark theme option, providing a visually appealing and comfortable user experience.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🎨 CUSTOMIZABLE INTERFACE:&lt;br>;Personalize your music experience with customizable widgets and interface colors. Control your music effortlessly from the status bar, widget, or headphone buttons, all tailored to your preferences.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🌐 OPEN-SOURCE TRANSPARENCY:&lt;br>;Your privacy is a top priority. Fossify Music Player operates completely offline, completely free of ads and does not request unnecessary permissions. Moreover, it is fully open-source, providing you with peace of mind, as you have access to the source code for security and privacy audits.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Experience music the way it's meant to be – uninterrupted, personalized, and immersive. Download Fossify Music Player now and embark on a musical journey like never before.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Explore more Fossify apps: https://www.fossify.org&lt;br>;Open-Source Code: https://www.github.com/FossifyOrg&lt;br>;Join the community on Reddit: https://www.reddit.com/r/Fossify&lt;br>;Connect on Telegram: https://t.me/Fossify&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.fossify.musicplayer/"/>
<summary>Open-source and Ad-free Music Player with customizable widget &amp; sleep timer</summary>
<published>2024-02-15T12:24:52+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/io.github.jica98/</id>
<title>DailyAL</title>
<updated>2024-02-15T12:20:00+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Jica98</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Durchsuchen Sie die riesige MyAnimeList-Datenbank und finden Sie Ihren Lieblings-Anime und Manga. Surfen Sie durch die Foren und finden Sie Millionen von Diskussionen auf Knopfdruck. Erhalten Sie detaillierte Rezensionen und finden Sie jede Menge Empfehlungen für alle Animes und Mangas in MyAnimeList.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;⚡️ Anime &amp; Manga ⚡️&lt;br>;&lt;br>;⭐ Saisonale Anime, kommende Top-Anime, beliebteste Anime, Anime-Rangliste, Favoriten aller Zeiten und mehr.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;⭐ Anime/Manga-Zusammenfassung. Verwandte und empfohlene Inhalte.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;⭐ Detaillierte Anime-Rezensionen und Anime-/Manga-Statistiken.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;⚡️ Theming und Anpassung⚡️&lt;br>;&lt;br>;⭐ Wählen Sie aus 4 verschiedenen dunklen Themen, nämlich Frühling, Sommer, Herbst und Winter.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;⭐ Passen Sie sogar die untere Navigationsleiste und die Aktualisierungshäufigkeit des Caches an.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;⚡️ MyAnimeList-Foren ⚡️&lt;br>;&lt;br>;⭐ Foren zu MyAnimeList, Anime und Manga und sogar allgemeine Diskussionen.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;⚡️ Erweiterte Suchleiste⚡️&lt;br>;&lt;br>;⭐ Führen Sie mithilfe von „@“ „#“ ganz einfach erweiterte Suchen direkt über die Suchleiste durch.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;⭐ Schnellere Ladezeiten für die Suche mithilfe von Caching-Mechanismen.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;⚡️Benutzerspezifische Funktionen⚡️&lt;br>;&lt;br>;⭐ Bearbeiten/aktualisieren Sie Ihre Anime-/Manga-Liste innerhalb von Sekunden.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;⭐ Sortieren Sie Ihre Liste nach Titel, Listenpunktzahl, Startdatum und Aktualisierungsdatum.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/io.github.jica98/"/>
<summary>Full featured MyAnimeList client made with flutter</summary>
<published>2024-02-15T12:20:00+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.logseq.app/</id>
<title>Logseq</title>
<updated>2024-02-15T12:11:02+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Logseq dev team</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Logseq is a knowledge management and collaboration platform. It focuses on privacy, longevity, and user control. Logseq offers a range of powerful tools for knowledge management, collaboration, PDF annotation, and task management with support for multiple file formats, including Markdown and Org-mode, and various features for organizing and structuring your notes.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Logseq's Whiteboard feature lets you organize your knowledge and ideas using a spatial canvas with shapes, drawings, website embeds, and connectors. You can visually group and link your notes and external media (such as videos and images), enabling visual thinkers to compose, remix, annotate, and connect content from their knowledge base and emerging thoughts in a new way.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;In addition to its core features, Logseq has a growing ecosystem of plugins and themes that enable a wide range of workflows and customization options. Mobile apps are also available, providing access to most of the features of the desktop application. Whether you're a student, a professional, or anyone who values a clear and organized approach to managing your ideas and notes, Logseq is an excellent choice for anyone looking to improve their productivity and streamline their workflow.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.logseq.app/"/>
<summary>A privacy-first, open-source platform for knowledge management and collaboration</summary>
<published>2024-02-15T12:11:02+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.codeberg.quecomet.oshi/</id>
<title>Oshi Uploader</title>
<updated>2024-02-11T03:03:14+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>quecomet</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Oshi Uploader Android Client&lt;br>;&lt;br>;App features:&lt;br>;- Add your own oshi instances or use the publicly available one by default (oshi.at)&lt;br>;- You can enable fingerprint check for SSL certificates&lt;br>;- Manage your uploaded files&lt;br>;- Keep a history of uploaded files&lt;br>;- Share from other apps to create uploads (including text)&lt;br>;- Do the upload in background and see the progress in notification&lt;br>;- Fully open source&lt;br>;&lt;br>;open-source repo link:&lt;br>;https://codeberg.org/quecomet/oshi/&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.codeberg.quecomet.oshi/"/>
<summary>an Android app that can upload to any Oshi instance</summary>
<published>2024-02-11T03:03:14+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/me.sujanpoudel.playdeals/</id>
<title>Play Deals</title>
<updated>2024-02-11T03:00:39+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Sujan Poudel</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Mit Play Deals finden Sie die neuesten App-Angebote und Rabatte für kostenpflichtige Apps. Sie können kostenpflichtige Apps finden, die jetzt kostenlos heruntergeladen werden können oder einen Rabatt bieten.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Merkmale:&lt;br>;‣ Klares Design mit Unterstützung für den Nachtmodus&lt;br>;‣ Neue Apps werden ständig hinzugefügt&lt;br>;‣ Apps werden auf Ablauf überprüft, sodass Sie nur gültige Apps sehen&lt;br>;‣ Apps nach ihren Kategorien filtern&lt;br>;‣ Finden Sie App-Preisangebote&lt;br>;‣ Teilen Sie das App-Angebot, das Sie kennen&lt;br>;‣ Erhalten Sie Benachrichtigungen für alle App-Angebote&lt;br>;‣ Fügen Sie Angebote für die App hinzu, die Sie kennen&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Die tatsächlichen Preise können je nach Standort leicht variieren.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Hinweis: Dies ist kein App Store. Sie können keine APKs oder ähnliches von dieser App herunterladen. Sie erhalten lediglich den Link zur entsprechenden App.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Wenn Sie Vorschläge oder Feedback haben, kontaktieren Sie mich bitte unter feedback@sujanpoudel.me&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/me.sujanpoudel.playdeals/"/>
<summary>Find the latest app deals and discounts on paid apps and games.</summary>
<published>2024-02-11T03:00:39+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/garden.lina.oblique_strategies/</id>
<title>Oblique Strategies</title>
<updated>2024-02-19T13:49:00+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>hobgoblina</name>
</author>
<content type="html">A deck of cards.&lt;br>;Over one hundred worthwhile dilemmas.&lt;br>;Insights into creative processes.&lt;br>;Gnomic challenges, constraints, and questions for you to interpret.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;First published by Brian Eno and Peter Schmidt in 1975, Oblique Strategies is a tool for working past creative blocks and reorienting (or disorienting) thought processes.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;This app presents you with a single strategy card at a time.&lt;br>;- Swipe to reveal the next card.&lt;br>;- Use the back button to bring previous cards back.&lt;br>;- Create recurring notifications.&lt;br>;- Favorites cards to change how frequently they occur.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/garden.lina.oblique_strategies/"/>
<summary>Over one hundred worthwhile dilemmas</summary>
<published>2024-02-11T02:56:46+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/eu.veldsoft.broker/</id>
<title>Broker 1961</title>
<updated>2024-02-11T02:56:22+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Velbazhd Software LLC</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Buy and sell stock shares. By play of Market Action cards, strategically manipulate prices to your advantage and to the downfall of your opponents. Win by having the most money in cash and stocks after the last card has been played. But be careful: if all of your remaining stock holdings crash, it is possible to be eliminated before the game is even over.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Originally published in 1961 as Broker by the Spencer-Murray Corporation of Swarthmore, Pennsylvania.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;The original box is white, with lettering and logo in black, very basic, drab, and uninspiring. Yet this obscure title was quite a gem considering the limitation of games to choose from during its day.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;In 1967 it was re-published by the German firm Otto Maier Verlag, which is the ancestor of Ravensburger Spieleverlag GmbH Verlag. Numerous re-publications followed (1972, 1977 and others) including at least one which gave the rules in German, English and Italian. It was also published in the Ravensburger Casino Series.&lt;br>;Components list for these editions are as follows: 160 stock certificates, 68 Market Action cards, 4 price markers, play money, stock price board.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;The 1983 (9th edition) by Ravensburger Spieleverlag GmbH changes the title slightly to Börsenspiel instead of Das Börsenspiel and the original rules heavily. Although this set is well-designed and much nicer on the eyes, the bland original version featured larger (regular card deck) size action cards. An extra set of 18 "risk" cards replacing 18 market cards had been added and they act as event cards that immediately effect changes in the market. They cause the unfortunate player who draws one to play it instead of a market card, a chaotic effect that some players will not like. Android version was implemented by Martin Kostadinov. It is school project for finish 12 grade.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/eu.veldsoft.broker/"/>
<summary>Very attractive board game which was created in 1961 for trading shares</summary>
<published>2024-02-11T02:56:22+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/de.marionoll.wgautoconnect/</id>
<title>WG Auto Connect</title>
<updated>2024-02-11T02:53:17+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Mario Noll</name>
</author>
<content type="html">WG Auto Connect is a small utility app that will automatically connect/disconnect to a specified WireGuard tunnel, once the connection to a pre selected network is lost/established.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/de.marionoll.wgautoconnect/"/>
<summary>Auto connect to a WireGuard tunnel</summary>
<published>2024-02-11T02:53:17+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.uravgcode.chooser/</id>
<title>Chooser</title>
<updated>2024-02-11T02:51:30+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>UrAvgCode</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Chooser ist eine Android-App um zufällig Finger auf dem Bildschirm auszuwählen, um zu entscheiden, wer an der Kasse bezahlen muss, wer bei einem Spiel anfängt, oder in welchen Teams man spielt.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Funktionen&lt;br>;&lt;br>;- Wähle eine zufällige Person aus&lt;br>;- Wähle mehrere Personen aus&lt;br>;- Teile Personen in Gruppen ein&lt;br>;- Zähle durch eine Gruppe durch&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.uravgcode.chooser/"/>
<summary>Android finger picker app</summary>
<published>2024-02-11T02:51:30+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.app.dailylog/</id>
<title>DailyLog</title>
<updated>2024-02-11T02:40:56+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">dailyLog is a distraction-free notepad with customizable shortcut buttons.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Tired of trying to log workouts on your phone? Want to build a custom habit tracker? Do you follow a template for every journal entry? dailyLog can help.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;dailyLog works by accessing a single text file of your choosing: keeping your data on your device and accessible in any app you choose. But unlike a blank text file, dailyLog lets you define custom shortcut buttons. Imagine a workout log where tapping the "chest" button pastes "chest press: reps, lbs", allowing you to log your workouts with ease. Or imagine a journal where the "📝" button pastes a list of questions you want to answer every day.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Initially designed as a rapid logging system for journaling, dailyLog allows you to quickly add info to a text file with customizable button shortcuts. See the detailed &lt;a href="https://github.com/madCode/dailylog#dailylog">;walkthrough with screenshots&lt;/a>; on the project homepage.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.app.dailylog/"/>
<summary>A quick-logging notes app with customizable shortcut buttons.</summary>
<published>2024-02-11T02:40:56+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.woheller69.whobird/</id>
<title>whoBIRD</title>
<updated>2024-02-17T08:13:18+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>woheller69</name>
</author>
<content type="html">whoBIRD ist der ultimativen Begleiter für Vogelbeobachtung, der Vögel weltweit anhand ihrer Gesänge erkennen kann!&lt;br>;Basierend auf dem innovativen BirdNET-Projekt verfügt whoBIRD über eine umfangreiche Datenbank mit über 6.000 Vogelarten weltweit.&lt;br>;Mithilfe fortschrittlicher maschineller Lernalgorithmen kann die App Vögel präzise anhand ihrer einzigartigen Lautäußerungen identifizieren.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Und das Beste daran: whoBIRD entfaltet seine Fähigkeiten komplett auf Ihrem Gerät, ohne eine Internetverbindung zu benötigen.&lt;br>;Das bedeutet, Sie können es jederzeit und überall nutzen – sei es tief im Wald oder am Ufer eines abgelegenen Sees.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.woheller69.whobird/"/>
<summary>Recognize birds by their sounds, anywhere in the world!</summary>
<published>2024-02-06T11:42:11+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/eu.mirkodi.swatchbeatclock/</id>
<title>Swatch .beat clock</title>
<updated>2024-02-17T08:02:45+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>mirk0dex</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Are you tired of the boring old 24-hour format? Could you use some change in your life?&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Let me introduce you to the &lt;b>;Swatch Internet Time&lt;/b>; format!&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Instead of dividing the day into 24 hours, it divides it into 1000 .beat's. 6:00 AM becomes "@250", 11:27 PM becomes "@977" and so on! In addition to that, there are no timezones in Internet Time. It's the same all over the world. It's based on Biel Mean Time (BMT), similar to Central European Time (CET).&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Of course, getting used to this new format might not be easy, and even when you learn it, you will still need a .beat clock.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;That's where the Swatch .beat clock app comes into place. With a handy converter and a fully functional digital clock, it will help you through your journey.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Read more about Internet Time on &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Swatch_Internet_Time">;Wikipedia&lt;/a>;.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/eu.mirkodi.swatchbeatclock/"/>
<summary>Internet Time clock and converter</summary>
<published>2024-02-06T11:31:08+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/dubrowgn.microtimer/</id>
<title>Micro Timer</title>
<updated>2024-02-06T11:30:39+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">&lt;i>;Micro Timer&lt;/i>; is a tiny, microwave-inspired timer app for Android. Instead of inventing yet another clever, pretty, tedious method of inputing time, &lt;i>;Micro Timer&lt;/i>; uses the tried-and-true 10-key pad commonly found on microwave ovens.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/dubrowgn.microtimer/"/>
<summary>A tiny, microwave-inspired timer app for Android</summary>
<published>2024-02-06T11:30:39+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.github.lamarios.clipious/</id>
<title>Clipious</title>
<updated>2024-02-15T12:08:44+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Paul Fauchon</name>
</author>
<content type="html">&lt;p>;&lt;i>;Clipious&lt;/i>;is an Android client for Invidious, the privacy focused YouTube front end.&lt;/p>;&lt;p>;&lt;b>;Features:&lt;/b>;&lt;/p>;&lt;ul>;&lt;li>;Use own or public server&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;Subscription management&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;SponsorBlock + DeArrow&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;Video view/progress tracking&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;User playlists&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;Background playback&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;Live stream support&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;Android TV UI&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;Audio playback&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;Video / audio download&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;Video filtering&lt;/li>;&lt;li>;Return Youtube Dislikes&lt;/li>;&lt;/ul>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.github.lamarios.clipious/"/>
<summary>Client for Invidious, the privacy focused YouTube front end.</summary>
<published>2024-02-06T11:20:06+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.fhs.ksre/</id>
<title>Katawa Shoujo: Re-Engineered</title>
<updated>2024-02-06T11:19:03+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Fleeting Heartbeat Studios</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Katawa Shoujo (translated "Disability Girls") is a bishōjo-style visual novel by Four Leaf Studios that tells the story of a young man and five young women living with varying disabilities. The game uses a traditional text and sprite-based visual novel model with an ADV-style text box running on the Ren'Py visual novel engine. The game is licensed under the Creative Commons CC-BY-NC-ND.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Katawa Shoujo: Re-Engineered offers a battery of accessibility features to accommodate players with disabilities. Using the tools available in modern Ren’Py, we’ve added quick access to self-voicing, two dyslexic typefaces, a special high contrast text box, and various optimizations to improve functionality with common screenreaders- and that’s just the beginning. We’re already looking into other ways to make KS:RE even more accessible.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Open source. No archives. No obfuscation. KS:RE doesn’t try to hide how it works. Anyone is welcome to peek under the hood and experiment, free of interference. The vastly simplified codebase of KS:RE allows developers of all skill levels to read, learn, and alter to their heart’s content. If you have an idea- a new accessibility feature, an improvement to a menu, a further simplification of the code- you have everything you need to make it happen. KS:RE is a community project first and foremost. If you can make the game better, our door is always open.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;KS:RE, under its default settings, plays exactly as you remember it. However, you have a few new options at your fingertips to tailor your experience to your liking. For a touch of visual flair, you can enable Parallax viewing, breathing a little extra life into your favorite characters. Sharing your experience has never been simpler - KS:RE seamlessly integrates with Discord’s activity bar, letting your friends see your excellent taste in visual novels. All of these features are completely optional, and can be toggled with a single click.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;KS:RE comes preloaded with Russian, French, Spanish translations, ready to use with no extra effort on the player’s end. Every other official translation won’t be far behind. The simplified codebase of KS:RE makes creating new translations easier than ever, requiring virtually zero programming knowledge. We’re more than willing to port over any finished translation you create and add it to KS:RE- credited to you, of course.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.fhs.ksre/"/>
<summary>(18+) A fan-made modernization of the classic visual novel</summary>
<published>2024-02-06T11:19:03+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.eclipse.kuksa.companion/</id>
<title>KUKSA Companion App</title>
<updated>2024-02-19T13:54:23+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Eclipse Kuksa</name>
</author>
<content type="html">The KUKSA Companion App demonstrates the capabilities of the Android SDK to connect to a vehicle with an integrated KUKSA Databroker, read data and interact with the actuators of the vehicle. The KUKSA framework is based on the COVESA Vehicle Signal Specification (VSS).&lt;br>;&lt;br>;The VSS defines the names and semantics of a large set of data entries that represent the current and/or intended state of a vehicle's sensors and actuators organized in a tree-like structure. For example, the vehicle's current speed is represented by the Vehicle.Speed entry.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;However, VSS does not define how these signals are to be collected and managed within a vehicle, nor does it prescribe how other components in the vehicle can read or write signal values from and to the tree.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;The KUKSA Databroker is a resource efficient implementation of the VSS signal tree and is intended to be run within a vehicle on a microprocessor based platform. It allows applications in the vehicle to interact with the vehicle's sensors and actuators using a uniform, high level gRPC API for querying signals, updating current and target values of sensors and actuators and getting notified about changes to signals of interest.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Showcases covered by the Companion App are:&lt;br>;&lt;br>;- Door Control&lt;br>;- Temperature Control&lt;br>;- Light Control&lt;br>;- Tire Pressure Check&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Find out more about KUKSA:&lt;br>;&lt;br>;- Vehicle Signal Specification: https://covesa.github.io/vehicle_signal_specification/&lt;br>;- KUKSA Databroker: https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.val/&lt;br>;- KUKSA Android SDK: https://github.com/eclipse-kuksa/kuksa-android-sdk/&lt;br>;- KUKSA Companion App: https://github.com/eclipse-kuksa/kuksa-android-companion/&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.eclipse.kuksa.companion/"/>
<summary>The Companion App for the KUKSA Databroker.</summary>
<published>2024-02-02T16:01:43+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.b3log.siyuan/</id>
<title>SiYuan</title>
<updated>2024-02-15T12:23:31+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Yunnan Liandi Technology Co., Ltd.</name>
</author>
<content type="html">思源笔记是一款隐私优先的个人知识管理系统，支持细粒度块级引用和 Markdown 所见即所得。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;&lt;h3>;特性&lt;/h3>;&lt;br>;大部分功能是免费的，即使是在商业环境下使用&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;内容块&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;块级引用和双向链接&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;自定义属性&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;SQL 查询嵌入&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;协议 &lt;code>;siyuan://&lt;/code>;&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;编辑器&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Block 风格&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Markdown 所见即所得&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;列表大纲&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;块缩放聚焦&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;块横向排版&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;百万字大文档编辑&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;数学公式、图表、流程图、甘特图、时序图、五线谱等&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;网页剪藏&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;PDF 标注双链&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;导出&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;引用块和嵌入块&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;带 assets 文件夹的标准 Markdown&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;PDF、Word 和 HTML&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;复制到微信公众号、知乎和语雀&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;数据库&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;表格视图&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;间隔重复&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;模板片段&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;JavaScript/CSS 代码片段&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Android/iOS APP&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Docker 部署&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;API&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;社区集市&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;br>;部分功能需要付费会员才能使用，更多细节请参考定价。&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.b3log.siyuan/"/>
<summary>隐私优先的个人知识管理系统</summary>
<published>2024-02-02T16:00:42+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/dev.imranr.obtainium.fdroid/</id>
<title>Obtainium</title>
<updated>2024-02-11T02:54:48+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Imran</name>
</author>
<content type="html">&lt;p>;Obtainium allows you to install and update Apps directly from their releases pages, and receive notifications when new releases are made available.&lt;/p>;&lt;br>;&lt;p>;Read the &lt;a href="https://github.com/ImranR98/Obtainium/wiki">;Wiki&lt;/a>;&lt;/p>;&lt;br>;&lt;p>;&lt;br>;	&lt;b>;Currently supported App sources:&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;/p>;&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;	&lt;li>;&lt;br>;		&lt;p>;Open Source - General:&lt;/p>;&lt;br>;		&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;GitHub&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;GitLab&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;Codeberg&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;F-Droid&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;Third Party F-Droid Repos&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;IzzyOnDroid&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;SourceForge&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;SourceHut&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;		&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;	&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;	&lt;li>;&lt;br>;		&lt;p>;Other - General:&lt;/p>;&lt;br>;		&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;APKPure&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;Aptoide&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;Uptodowng&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;APKMirror (Track-Only)&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;Huawei AppGallery&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;Jenkins Jobs&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;		&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;	&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;	&lt;li>;&lt;br>;		&lt;p>;Open Source - App-Specific:&lt;/p>;&lt;br>;		&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;Mullvad&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;Signal&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;VLC&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;		&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;	&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;	&lt;li>;&lt;br>;		&lt;p>;Other - App-Specific:&lt;/p>;&lt;br>;		&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;WhatsApp&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;Telegram App&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;			&lt;li>;Neutron Code&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;		&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;	&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;	&lt;li>;&lt;p>;"HTML" (Fallback): Any other URL that returns an HTML page with links to APK files&lt;/p>;&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;p>;&lt;br>;	&lt;b>;Limitations:&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;/p>;&lt;br>;&lt;p>;&lt;br>;	For some sources, data is gathered using Web scraping and can easily break due to changes in website design. In such cases, more reliable methods may be unavailable.&lt;br>;&lt;/p>;&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/dev.imranr.obtainium.fdroid/"/>
<summary>Get android app updates directly from the source</summary>
<published>2024-02-02T15:53:12+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.sanmer.mrepo/</id>
<title>MRepo</title>
<updated>2024-02-15T12:13:10+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Sanmer</name>
</author>
<content type="html">MRepo is an Android app that helps manage your own modules repository.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Features:&lt;br>;- Manage your modules repository&lt;br>;- Support multiple repositories&lt;br>;- Support Magisk and KernelSU&lt;br>;- Jetpack Compose &amp; Material Design 3&lt;br>;&lt;br>;https://github.com/MRepoApp/MRepo</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.sanmer.mrepo/"/>
<summary>A Manager for Magisk &amp; KernelSU Modules</summary>
<published>2024-02-02T15:47:06+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.guozhigq.pilipala/</id>
<title>PiliPala</title>
<updated>2024-02-06T11:21:25+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>guozhigq</name>
</author>
<content type="html">PiliPala 是使用 Flutter 开发的 BiliBili 第三方客户端。&lt;br>;&lt;br>;主要功能：&lt;br>;&lt;br>;* 推荐视频列表 (app 端)&lt;br>;* 最热视频列表&lt;br>;* 热门直播&lt;br>;* 番剧列表&lt;br>;* 屏蔽黑名单内用户视频&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.guozhigq.pilipala/"/>
<summary>使用 Flutter 开发的 BiliBili 第三方客户端</summary>
<published>2024-02-02T15:42:51+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.cappielloantonio.notquitemy.tempo/</id>
<title>Tempo</title>
<updated>2024-02-02T15:39:18+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>AntonioCappiello</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Tempo is an open-source and lightweight music client for Subsonic, designed and built natively for Android. It provides a seamless and intuitive music streaming experience, allowing you to access and play your Subsonic music library directly from your Android device.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Features&lt;br>;&lt;br>;- Subsonic Integration: Tempo seamlessly integrates with your Subsonic server, providing you with easy access to your entire music collection on the go.&lt;br>;- Sleek and Intuitive UI: Enjoy a clean and user-friendly interface designed to enhance your music listening experience, tailored to your preferences and listening history.&lt;br>;- Browse and Search: Easily navigate through your music library using various browsing and searching options, including artists, albums, genres, playlists, decades and more.&lt;br>;- Streaming and Offline Mode: Stream music directly from your Subsonic server. Offline mode is currently under active development and may have limitations when using multiple servers.&lt;br>;- Playlist Management: Create, edit, and manage playlists to curate your perfect music collection.&lt;br>;- Gapless Playback: Experience uninterrupted playback with gapless listening mode.&lt;br>;- Chromecast Support: Stream your music to Chromecast devices. The support is currently in a rudimentary state.&lt;br>;- Scrobbling Integration: Optionally integrate Tempo with Last.fm to scrobble your played tracks, gather music insights, and further personalize your music recommendations, if supported by your Subsonic server.&lt;br>;- Podcasts and Radio: If your Subsonic server supports it, listen to podcasts and radio shows directly within Tempo, expanding your audio entertainment options.&lt;br>;- Transcoding Support: Activate transcoding of tracks on your Subsonic server, allowing you to set a transcoding profile for optimized streaming directly from the app. This feature requires support from your Subsonic server.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.cappielloantonio.notquitemy.tempo/"/>
<summary>An open-source and lightweight music client for Subsonic</summary>
<published>2024-02-02T15:39:18+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.futo.circles/</id>
<title>Circles</title>
<updated>2024-02-06T11:38:16+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>FUTO</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Circles combines the ease of use and convenience of an online social network with the privacy and security of an encrypted messenger.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;All posts are encrypted end-to-end, and there are no ads and no tracking.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Connect with the people who truly matter in your life, without creepy ad networks spying on every interaction.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Safely share photos of your kids with grandparents, aunts and uncles, friends and other family members.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.futo.circles/"/>
<summary>Secure social sharing for friends and families</summary>
<published>2024-01-30T17:58:57+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/micro.repl.ma7moud3ly/</id>
<title>Micro REPL</title>
<updated>2024-01-30T17:55:33+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>ma7moud3ly</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Micro REPL has the following features:&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;A &lt;strong>;Terminal&lt;/strong>; to access MicroPython interactive interpreter.&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Files &lt;strong>;Explorer&lt;/strong>; (Files Manager) for MicroPython storage.&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;A Smart &lt;strong>;Code Editor&lt;/strong>; with python syntax support and code completion.&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/micro.repl.ma7moud3ly/"/>
<summary>MicroPython IDE</summary>
<published>2024-01-30T17:55:33+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/io.github.saeeddev94.xray/</id>
<title>Xray</title>
<updated>2024-02-19T13:50:28+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>SaeedDev94</name>
</author>
<content type="html">This is a simple GUI client for XTLS/Xray-core&lt;br>;Also you can use it independent of Xray-core just for your socks proxy (Like SocksDroid)&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/io.github.saeeddev94.xray/"/>
<summary>Xray GUI Client For Android</summary>
<published>2024-01-30T17:53:38+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.myclosetx/</id>
<title>Closet-Archive</title>
<updated>2024-01-30T17:43:56+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Bahaa Tuffaha</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Features&lt;br>;&lt;br>;- Adding a Clothing Item.&lt;br>;- Filtring clothes.&lt;br>;- Logging an Event.&lt;br>;- Managing Collections.&lt;br>;- Laundry alert/notification.&lt;br>;- "Import" and "Export" your data localy.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.myclosetx/"/>
<summary>Organize clothes, log events, track laundry, and recall last week's outfit.</summary>
<published>2024-01-30T17:43:56+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.hassaneltantawy.hisnelmoslem/</id>
<title>Hisn Elmoslem</title>
<updated>2024-01-30T17:41:09+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Hassan Eltantawy</name>
</author>
<content type="html">- With a simple interface and completely without ads&lt;br>;- It supports many color mode.&lt;br>;- Search Zikr.&lt;br>;- Add or remove zikr from favourites.&lt;br>;- Add alarm to each zikr.&lt;br>;- Sound and vibrate on zikr finish.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.hassaneltantawy.hisnelmoslem/"/>
<summary>You favourite app to azkar.</summary>
<published>2024-01-30T17:41:09+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.app.openlib/</id>
<title>Openlib</title>
<updated>2024-02-13T13:09:00+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>dstark</name>
</author>
<content type="html">&lt;p>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;&lt;i>;Openlib&lt;/i>;&lt;/b>; is an open source app to download and read books from shadow library (&lt;a href='https://annas-archive.org/' target='_blank' rel='nofollow noopener'>;Anna’s Archive&lt;/a>;). The App Has Built In Reader to Read Books.&lt;br>;&lt;/p>;&lt;br>;&lt;p>;&lt;br>;As &lt;i>;Anna’s Archive&lt;/i>; doesn't have an API, the app works by sending requests to &lt;i>;Anna’s Archive&lt;/i>; and parses the response to objects. The app extracts the mirrors from the responses, downloads the book and stores it in the application's document directory.&lt;br>;&lt;/p>;&lt;br>;&lt;p>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;Note :&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;The app requires VPN to function properly . Without VPN the might show the captcha required page even after completing the captcha&lt;br>;&lt;/p>;&lt;br>;&lt;b>;&lt;p>;Main Features:&lt;/p>;&lt;/b>;&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Trending Books&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Download And Read Books With In-Built Viewer&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Supports Epub And Pdf Formats&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Open Books With Your Favourite Ebooks Reader&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Filter Books&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;li>;Sort Books&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.app.openlib/"/>
<summary>download and read books from shadow library (Anna’s Archive)</summary>
<published>2024-01-30T17:36:43+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/ch.simonste.jasstafel/</id>
<title>Jass board</title>
<updated>2024-02-02T15:36:42+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Simon Steinmann</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Jass Tafel um die Punkte beim Jassen einfach mit dem Android-Smartphone oder Tablet zu zählen.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Es ist möglich die Punkte beim Schieber, Coiffeur, Differenzler, Molotow und weiteren Jassarten zu schreiben. &lt;br>;&lt;br>;Die Eingabemenüs sind so gestaltet, dass es möglich ist mit einer minimalen Anzahl an Klicks die Punkte zu schreiben.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;*************************&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Für alle Tafeln ist es möglich mehrere Profile zu führen. Einstellungen und Punktestände werden unabhängig gespeichert. So muss z.B. eine noch nicht beendete Runde nicht gelöscht werden um mit anderen Spielern zu Jassen. Auch wenn je nach Zusammensetzung nach unterschiedliche Regeln gespielt wird kann dies einfach über ein Profil gelöst werden.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Das aktuelle Profil kann per AndroidBeam (NFC) auch einfach mit einem anderen Gerät geteilt werden. Dazu muss bei einem Gerät die Tafel geöffnet sein und die Geräte müssen Rücken an Rücken zueinander gehalten werden. Das ist z.B. bei leerem Akku oder aufwendigen Profileinstellungen hilfreich.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Ebenfalls für alle Tafeln gibt es die Möglichkeit anzugeben wer als nächstes die Karten austeilen soll. Dazu gibt es im Statistik-Dialog ein 'Portrait'-Icon. Die Reihenfolge und wer zuerst dran ist muss natürlich initial mal festgelegt werden. Anschliessend wird aber automatisch nachgeführt. Dies soll helfen, wenn man sich mal nicht mehr erinnern kann wer dran ist. &lt;br>;&lt;br>;*************************&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Schiebertafel:&lt;br>;- Punkte einzeln schreiben (1/20/50/100) für Weis,...&lt;br>;- Komplette Runden schreiben inkl. Multiplikator (1x-7x) und Gegnerpunkte&lt;br>;- Eingabedialog kann gedreht werden (für 1 bzw. 2 Schreiber)&lt;br>;- Einzelne Eingaben oder auch komplette Runden können rückgängig gemacht werden.&lt;br>;- Verschiedene Zielpunktezahlen möglich (z.B Bieter)&lt;br>;- Einstellbare Punktzahl pro Runde (z.B für Doppelkarten 314)&lt;br>;- Umfangreiche Statistiken&lt;br>;- Rückseite um Sieg/Match,... Striche zu notieren&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Coiffeurtafel:&lt;br>;- Die Jassarten können nach eigenen Vorlieben gewählt werden.&lt;br>;- 16 vordefinierte Jassarten + die Möglichkeit eine eigene einzugeben (ohne Bild).&lt;br>;- Die Anzahl gespielter Runden kann zwischen 6 und 12 liegen.&lt;br>;- Es kann für 2 oder 3 Teams geschrieben werden.&lt;br>;- Multiplikatoren können manuell geändert werden falls gewünscht.&lt;br>;- Statistiken über erreichbare Punkte sowie Bedingungen wie ein Team uneinholbar wird.&lt;br>;- Wenn ein Team uneinholbar ist, wird dies angezeigt.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Differenzlertafel:&lt;br>;- 2-8 Spieler&lt;br>;- Ansagen bleiben verborgen bis die ersten Punkte eingegeben wurden.&lt;br>;- Punkte vom letzten ausstehenden Spieler werden automatisch berechnet.&lt;br>;- Punkte der letzten Runde können nachträglich geändert werden (Lang Drücken)&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Molotowtafel:&lt;br>;- 2-8 Spieler&lt;br>;- Schreiben von Weisen in 3 Klicks&lt;br>;- Beim Runden schreiben werden die ausstehenden Punkte automatisch berechnet.&lt;br>;- Punkte nachträglich editierbar (Lang Drücken)&lt;br>;- Punkte können exakt oder gerundet geschrieben werden.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Punktetafel:&lt;br>;Dies ist eine möglichst allgemeine Schreibtafel, die es erlauben sollte viele weitere Jassarten zu schreiben.&lt;br>;- 2-8 Spieler&lt;br>;- Zielpunkte / Anzahl Runden kann eingestellt werden&lt;br>;- Um schneller schreiben zu können kann die Anzahl Punkte pro Runde eingestellt werden. (Ausstehende Punkte werden automatisch berechnet).&lt;br>;&lt;br>;*************************&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Der Quellcode der App ist online verfügbar:&lt;br>;https://github.com/simonste/jasstafel</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/ch.simonste.jasstafel/"/>
<summary>Very flexible Jass board to write points at the Schieber, Coiffeur, Molotov.</summary>
<published>2024-01-30T17:34:33+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/ch.mydoli.focal/</id>
<title>FoCal</title>
<updated>2024-01-30T17:33:51+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>MYDOLI</name>
</author>
<content type="html">FoCal is a free (as in freedom) Android application for keeping a Photo Calendar.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Import daily pictures, consistently journal about your life and enjoy a satisfying retrospective view of every month.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;• Keep everything private and local, it is your personal calendar&lt;br>;• Display the app in dark or light theme&lt;br>;• Use photos from your gallery or enable direct camera imports&lt;br>;• Export and import your entire database for backup or migration&lt;br>;• Support 100% Free and Open Source software, with no proprietary dependencies&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/ch.mydoli.focal/"/>
<summary>FoCal enables you to create your personal photo calendar</summary>
<published>2024-01-30T17:33:51+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/app.simple.peri/</id>
<title>Peristyle</title>
<updated>2024-02-15T12:03:13+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Hamza Rizwan</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Peristyle is created to be extremely simple and sophisticated wallpaper manager and browser app for Android. It solves the problem of having too many features and bloated apps and having very minimal support for locally stored wallpapers. What if you just wanted an app that allows you to browse and select your own locally stored wallpapers and lets you manage and set wallpapers from there? then Peristyle is for you :)&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Features:&lt;br>;&lt;br>;- Simple architecture, browse wallpapers and use system wallpaper manager to set them as wallpaper.&lt;br>;- Can scan .nomedia directories, useful if you want to keep your wallpapers away from gallery.&lt;br>;- Apply blur and color filters dynamically on any wallpaper before applying.&lt;br>;- Simple yet pretty animations with proper optimizations&lt;br>;- No ads, no tracking, no analytics, no internet permissions, no unnecessary permissions&lt;br>;- Auto wallpaper change support&lt;br>;- Dark mode support&lt;br>;- Biometric authentication support&lt;br>;- Fully Material You design&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/app.simple.peri/"/>
<summary>Simple wallpaper manager app with auto wallpaper support.</summary>
<published>2024-01-30T17:33:08+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/us.spotco.carrion/</id>
<title>Carrion</title>
<updated>2024-02-17T08:14:30+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Divested Computing Group</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Automatically rejects all calls failing STIR/SHAKEN verification. Requires official support for Android 11 or higher, working VoLTE, and carrier support.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/us.spotco.carrion/"/>
<summary>Block spoofed calls</summary>
<published>2024-01-26T21:18:40+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.fossify.messages/</id>
<title>Fossify SMS Messenger</title>
<updated>2024-02-13T13:29:19+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Fossify</name>
</author>
<content type="html">El Fossify Messenger és el vostre company de missatgeria de confiança, dissenyat per a millorar l'experiència de missatgeria de diverses maneres.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;📱 MANTENIU-VOS EN CONNECTE AMB FACILITAT:&lt;br>;Amb el Fossify Messenger podeu enviar missatges SMS i MMS sense cap esforç per a mantenir-vos en connecte amb els éssers estimats. Gaudiu de la missatgeria en grup basada en SMS/MMS i expresseu-vos amb fotos, emojis i salutacions ràpides.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🚫 BLOQUEU ELS MISSATGES NO DESITJATS:&lt;br>;Preneu el control de la vostra experiència de missatgeria amb una característica de bloqueig robusta, evitant fàcilment els missatges no desitjats, fins i tot de contactes desconeguts. També podeu exportar i importar números bloquejats fent una còpia de seguretat sense complicacions. A més, personalitzeu l'experiència evitant que els missatges amb paraules o frases específiques arribin a la safata d'entrada.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🔒 CÒPIA DE SEGURETAT DE SMS SENSE ESFORÇ:&lt;br>;Acomiadeu-vos de les preocupacions per perdre missatges importants. El Fossify Messenger ofereix una funcionalitat de còpia de seguretat d'SMS còmoda, permetent-vos exportar i importar els vostres missatges. Aquesta característica garanteix que podeu canviar fàcilment els dispositius sense perdre les vostres converses valuoses.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🚀 RÀPID COM UN LLAMP I LLEUGER:&lt;br>;Tot i les seves característiques potents, el Fossify Messenger té una mida d'aplicació notablement petita, que la fa ràpida i fàcil de descarregar i instal·lar. Experimenteu la velocitat i l'eficiència mentre gaudiu de la tranquil·litat que comporta la còpia de seguretat dels SMS.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🔐 PRIVADESA MILLORADA:&lt;br>;Personalitzeu el que apareix a la pantalla de bloqueig per a més privacitat. Trieu mostrar només el remitent, el contingut del missatge o res en absolut. Els missatges estan sota el vostre control.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🔍 CERCA EFICIENT DE MISSATGES:&lt;br>;Digueu adeu a la infinitat de desplaçaments a través de les converses. El Fossify Messenger simplifica la recuperació de missatges amb una característica de cerca ràpida i eficient. Trobeu el que necessiteu, quan ho necessiteu.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🌈 «MODERN DESSIGN» I INTERFÍCIE FÀCIL D'UTILITZAR:&lt;br>;Gaudiu d'un disseny net i modern amb una interfície fàcil d'utilitzar. L'aplicació compta amb el «material design» i una opció de tema fosc, proporcionant una experiència d'usuari visualment atractiva i còmoda.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🌐 TRANSPARÈNCIA DEL CODI OBERT:&lt;br>;La teva privacitat és una prioritat absoluta. El Fossify Messenger opera sense necessitat de connexió a Internet, garantint la seguretat i l'estabilitat dels missatges. La nostra aplicació està totalment lliure d'anuncis i no sol·licita permisos innecessaris. A més, és totalment de codi obert, proporcionant-vos tranquil·litat, ja que teniu accés al codi font per a auditories de seguretat i privacitat.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Feu el canvi al Fossify Messenger i experimenteu la missatgeria de la manera com ha de ser: privada, eficient i fàcil d'utilitzar. Descarregueu-la ara i uniu-vod a la nostra comunitat compromesa amb la salvaguarda de la vostra experiència de la missatgeria.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Exploreu més aplicacions de Fossify: https://www.fossify.org&lt;br>;Codi obert: https://www.github.com/FossifyOrg&lt;br>;Uniu-vos a la comunitat a Reddit: https://www.reddit.com/r/Fossify&lt;br>;Connecteu a Telegram: https://t.me/Fossify&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.fossify.messages/"/>
<summary>Open-source and Ad-free SMS/MMS messaging app</summary>
<published>2024-01-26T21:11:21+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/org.fossify.contacts/</id>
<title>Fossify Contacts</title>
<updated>2024-01-26T21:11:13+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Fossify</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Introducing Fossify Contacts - the next evolution in contact management. Poised to redefine how you manage your contacts, our app combines simplicity with advanced features, tailored for both personal and professional use.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🔍 SMART SEARCH &amp; FIELD CUSTOMIZATION:&lt;br>;Locate contacts quickly with our intelligent search feature. Customize visible fields, enjoy a user-friendly interface, and find contacts effortlessly, saving time and enhancing productivity.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;✉️ GROUP MANAGEMENT &amp; COMMUNICATION:&lt;br>;Effortlessly manage contact groups for streamlined communication. Our app facilitates easy grouping for batch emails or SMS, with features to create favorite lists and rename groups, enhancing your organizational capabilities.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🔄 RELIABLE BACKUP &amp; EXPORT OPTIONS:&lt;br>;Ensure your contacts are always safe with our reliable backup system. Seamlessly export or import contacts in vCard format, making data migration and backup a breeze.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🌐 OPEN-SOURCE TRANSPARENCY:&lt;br>;Built on an open-source platform, Fossify Contacts champions transparency and user trust. Access our code on GitHub and become part of a community that values privacy, openness, and collaborative improvement.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🖼️ PERSONALIZED USER EXPERIENCE:&lt;br>;Customize your contact management with ease. Our app offers flexible settings and design options, allowing you to tailor the interface to your liking. Sort contacts, choose themes, and personalize your experience for maximum convenience.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🔋 EFFICIENT &amp; LIGHTWEIGHT:&lt;br>;Optimized for performance, Fossify Contacts is designed to be light on your device's resources. It not only organizes your contacts efficiently but also contributes to longer battery life, ensuring smooth operation.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🚀 ADVANCED SYNCHRONIZATION:&lt;br>;Whether you choose to store your contacts locally or prefer syncing them across devices using different means, our app ensures a smooth, efficient, and secure management experience.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🔐 PRIVACY-FIRST APPROACH:&lt;br>;Your contact information remains confidential with Fossify Contacts. We prioritize your privacy, ensuring your data is never shared with third-party apps.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;🌙 MODERN DESIGN &amp; USER-FRIENDLY INTERFACE:&lt;br>;Enjoy a clean, modern design with a user-friendly interface. The app features a material design and a dark theme option, providing a visually appealing and comfortable user experience.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Download the app now and elevate your contact management to new heights. Your journey to efficient, secure, and intuitive contact organization begins here.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Explore more Fossify apps: https://www.fossify.org&lt;br>;Open-Source Code: https://www.github.com/FossifyOrg&lt;br>;Join the community on Reddit: https://www.reddit.com/r/Fossify&lt;br>;Connect on Telegram: https://t.me/Fossify&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/org.fossify.contacts/"/>
<summary>Manage your contacts privately and efficiently with vCard support</summary>
<published>2024-01-26T21:11:13+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/dev.maartje.hetsaldo/</id>
<title>Het Saldo</title>
<updated>2024-01-26T20:58:39+00:00</updated>
<author>
<name>Maartje Eyskens</name>
</author>
<content type="html">Het Saldo is a De Lijn "smart"card saldo checker.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;It allows you to easily keep track of the remaining trips on your De Lijn tickets. The app lets you add multiple tickets and syncs their status and remaining balance for you to check.</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/dev.maartje.hetsaldo/"/>
<summary>A cross-platform De Lijn "smart"ticket saldo checking application.</summary>
<published>2024-01-26T20:58:39+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/de.mlex.same/</id>
<title>Same</title>
<updated>2024-01-26T20:54:11+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">Same - It's a simple Game.&lt;br>;All fields must have the same color.&lt;br>;Press on a field to change it's color and that of the neighbouring fields.&lt;br>;Also in three-color mode.&lt;br>;The colors displayed can be changed randomly.&lt;br>;A long press on the colour palette resets the colors to their original color.&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/de.mlex.same/"/>
<summary>Two colors, nine fields. Make them all the same.</summary>
<published>2024-01-26T20:54:11+00:00</published>
</entry>
<entry>
<id>https://f-droid.org/packages/com.github.trilinder.tapasclient/</id>
<title>OpenTapasReader</title>
<updated>2024-01-26T20:44:39+00:00</updated>
<content type="html">Čtěte komiksy Tapas.io snadně.&lt;br>;&lt;br>;Features:&lt;br>;&lt;ul>;&lt;br>;  &lt;li>;Prohlížení komiksů a komiksových epizod&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;  &lt;li>;Stahování epizod pro použití offline&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;  &lt;li>;Čtení komentářů&lt;/li>;&lt;br>;&lt;/ul>;&lt;br>;</content>
<link href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.github.trilinder.tapasclient/"/>
<summary>Read Tapas.io comics (with offline support)</summary>
<published>2024-01-26T20:44:39+00:00</published>
</entry>
</feed>